DESTROY
DESTROYER
OF DEMONS
Tanjiro! Look out!
Oh, damn!
Zenitsu...
Forget about me!
This happened
because I wasn't paying attention!
I'm sorry, Inosuke!
If only I'd noticed him sooner!
No... I...
If I hadn't left Uzui's side in the first place,
this wouldn't have happened!
Sorry.
Sorry!
Sorry, everyone!
EPISODE 10:
NEVER GIVE UP
Sorry.
Sorry, everyone.
Sorry...
Nezuko.
Don't apologize, Big Bro.
Big Bro, why are you always apologizing?
If we're poor,
does that make us unhappy?
If we can't wear pretty kimonos,
should people pity us?
Are you so determined to blame someone?
You think it was our father's fault
for dying of illness.
He tried as hard as he could,
and it wasn't enough,
so we just have to accept that!
We're humans, after all, so none of us
can expect everything to go our way.
Whether you're happy or not is up to you.
The important thing is now.
Let's just look ahead.
Let's try harder together!
Let's fight!
Stop apologizing!
You of all people should understand!
I want you to understand how I feel!
Was that a dream about the past?
Huh? Where am I?
I...
This is awful.
I can't believe it ended up like this.
Were the people who live here
able to escape?
Where's Nezuko?
Nezuko...
Thanks, Nezuko.
I have to do what I can do!
UPPER SIX
What's this? You're still alive?
You're one lucky guy, huh?
Well, not that you have anything
going for you except for being lucky.
I feel sorry for you!
Everyone but you is probably done for!
A single thrust to that boar's heart.
That towheaded boy's trapped
under the rubble, and he's flailing,
so I'm just going to leave him there
until he dies.
Squirming like an insect...
How disgraceful is that!
And how weak was that Hashira!
All he had was bluster!
The poison got to him, stopping his heart,
and now he's dead! It's all over for him!
So disgraceful! So disgraceful!
You four are truly disgraceful!
Especially you!
You're in another league!
The one sticking out of that box
you carry is a relative, right?
I can tell that she's closely related to you
even if she's a demon now.
Is she your older or younger sister?
Why won't he kill me?
What is this?
My arm is numb!
I still have no strength!
Even if I went for his head now,
I couldn't slash it.
Nezuko...
is my younger sister.
Just as I thought!
You really are a disgrace!
You're not protecting
your little sister at all!
Well, I guess it can't be helped.
Since you're a human
and your sister's a demon.
Of course you're weaker
than your demon sister.
Even so, what a disgrace!
If you're her big bro,
instead of being protected by your little sister,
you should be protecting her!
Devotedly. With this hand, see?
Hey, listen!
How do you feel now?
Being the only one
to survive so disgracefully!
That little sister you rely on
has all but used up her strength!
Hey, worm! Dimwit!
Sad sack! Coward! Good-for-nothing!
Why were you even born, huh?
What are you gonna do?
With your weak sauce, battered, disgraceful
human body! Let's see you cut off my head!
Come on! Come on!
Come on!
Huh?
UPPER SIX
I see! Your soul got crushed
at the last minute, huh?
How disgraceful are you!
You're disgraceful as all get-out!
So disgraceful.
You really are one disgraceful guy.
I've never seen anyone
as disgraceful as you.
As disgraceful as you are,
I don't dislike you.
Because I like anything
that's pathetic, disgraceful and filthy!
This filthy scar on your forehead!
I like it! I think I'm getting attached to it!
I know! Why don't you
become a demon, too?
For your little sister's sake, as well!
That's it! That's it!
What a great idea!
If you become a demon,
I'll spare your life!
Because we'll be friends!
Otherwise, I'll slaughter your sister, too.
Since I really don't give a crap
about other people's little sisters.
No way! You'd better not, Brother!
I'm so not on board with that, all right?
If you become a demon,
you can become stronger, just like that!
You can kiss that defective
physical body goodbye!
Hey! Hey!
What's it gonna be?
Your own weakness
makes you bitter, doesn't it?
When humans grieve,
they look up to the sky.
You know, so their tears don't overflow.
I...
I was waiting for this moment!
A last-ditch head-butt, huh?
That had zero effect on me!
M-M-My body won't...
Brother, what are you doing?
Get on your feet!
Something's wrong!
What's going on? Something's wrong!
It was nothing
but a lame human head-butt!
A Kunai! I got stabbed
when he head-butted me!
This brat was pretending to run away
when he was really going for this Kunai!
Scattering the Courtesans' sachets
along with the rubble
to cover up the scent
of the Kunai's poison!
Damn you! Damn you!
You're a weakling!
A stinking human!
Look how beat-up you are after I rubbed
my superior strength in your face!
Why won't you give up
when you're on your own?
Why won't you cave in?
The will to bring me down...
Why is it so unswerving?
DEMON SLAYER: KIMETSU NO YAIBA
ENTERTAINMENT DISTRICT ARC
...Bro! Big Bro!
Big Bro!
Brother!
At every turn, one false step,
and I could've found myself
in that same situation.
I was lucky enough to remain a human,
but there could've been a future
in which we were both demons.
But even if I end up
turning into a demon, I'm sure...
that someone in the Demon Slayer Corps
will do me the favor of beheading me.
Cut through! Cut through!
Win! Win, no matter what!
We're going to win!
Hey! Are you kidding me?
Don't get beheaded
by someone like him!
Damn him! He pulled himself
out of the rubble!
Out of my way, ugly freak!
Thunder Breathing...
First Form...
I know how fast your move is!
I've seen it so many times!
Thunderclap and Flash...
Godlike Speed!
So fast!
M-My head's being severed!
Damn!
I didn't think he could move like this!
Cut through! Cut through!
Follow through!
I can only use Thunderclap and Flash Godlike Speed
twice! It saps the strength from my legs!
I've already used it once to escape
the rubble, so this is my last chance!
And I won't get another chance
to go for her neck if I don't do it now!
Tanjiro created this one-in-a-million chance!
I'm going to slash her for sure! For sure!
Dammit, I can't cut through!
It's too hard!
The poison should've weakened him!
Am I still not strong enough?
He's already recovered from the poison!
I'm being engulfed! I'll get slashed!
My sword's being repelled!
I was so close!
I was so close to...
Don't give up! Don't give up!
Don't give up!
Hang on! Until the end!
You little punk!
His attack speed...
is increasing!
He's breaking down the poison!
He's making a full recovery!
Don't give up!
Don't give—
He's not dead!
He wasn't dead!
His heart...
I get it!
He used his muscles
to force his heart to stop, huh?
That enabled him to temporarily stop
the poison from circulating!
Uzui!
I've finished my Musical Score Technique!
We're going for the win!
Don't make me laugh!
ICHI
SAN
SHICHI
GO
I
Ichi!
San! Shichi! Go! I! Kin!
I can read it!
That filthy score of yours!
He deflected all of my
Rotating Circular Slashes!
Amazing!
"Score"? Did he say "score"?
Did he turn my Blood Demon Art
into a song and deflect it?
When he only has one arm!
No way is this possible!
Don't give me this crap!
Amazing! He's holding his own!
But that's not enough to defeat him!
Uzui's going to reach his limit first!
I have to do it before that happens!
I have to cut off his neck!
Uzui!
Don't stop!
Jump!
You're too slow!
You little dumbass!
Even if you have someone to pave the way
for you, a loser is still a loser!
It's all over now!
The poison will kill you!
I'm gonna slash you!
I'm gonna behead you!
I'm not giving up!
I'm so going to behead you!
Damn you! Still swinging
your sword! You fool!
You couldn't behead me before!
What makes you think you can now?
I can't do it with just my arms! I have to slash him
with every ounce of strength I have!
From the top of my head
to the tips of my toes! Use it all!
Ignore all the pain in your body!
Hang on!
Striking with all your might
won't be enough!
One hundred times the force!
Summon it by force!
Crap! Not by a brat like him!
Dammit! I'm about to be beheaded!
No, I'm good!
Even if I get beheaded,
as long as my sister's head is still intact...
First, I'm going to finish this one off!
Dammit!
I have no more strength!
I'm going to chop you up into little pieces
before you can decapitate me!
What's he doing here?
Didn't my brother
impale him through the heart?
Don't underestimate
the flexibility of my body!
Shifting the position of my internal organs
is child's play for me!
And since I grew up on a harsh mountainside,
poison doesn't work on me, either!
Brother!
Do something, will you, Brother?
I have to unleash the Rotating Circular Slashes!
They beheaded them.
They beheaded them!
Beheaded them! Beheaded them!
They beheaded them, Hinatsuru!
Please take a look
from beyond the grave!
What the... Do you even know
what you're saying?
- What?
- Dummy!
Ouch!
Wait!
Something seems off about this!
Th-The poison...
Deal with it with your breathing!
S-Slow down the poison
as much as you can!
Kamado! Get up! It's not over yet!
What?
He's saying something.
His head...
Did I fail to cut it off after all?
Run! This isn't over yet!
Uzui is...
saying something.
Run!
NIN-NIN
Nin-nin!
Big Bro!
Big Bro, are you all right?
No, Brother! Live!
And now, it's time for a Taisho-era secret
about a certain something
that's helped my brother
overcome countless dangers like this!
My brother got his rock-hard head
from our mother!
When I was still a young child...
INOSUKE AS A BOAR
I hear...
that our mother once repulsed
a boar by head-butting him!
Next, the final episode,
"No Matter How Many Lives"!
Big Bro, I know you can do it!
Big Bro, I know you can win!
TO BE CONTINUED