DEMON SLAYER: KIMETSU NO YAIBA
MUGEN TRAIN ARC
EPISODE 1:
FLAME HASHIRA
KYOJURO RENGOKU
MISSING PERSON
NOODLES
Delicious!
Flame Hashira, forgive me
for interrupting your meal.
Okay! Take a seat here.
Mister, bring this young man
the same thing I'm having!
Are you sure it's okay?
Of course it's okay!
I'll have another bowl myself!
You sure eat with gusto, don't you?
Just sit tight.
Flame Hashira,
your work last night was stellar.
No.
It was after the demon fled, after all.
How's the injured woman doing?
According to the doctor,
her wounds won't leave her with any scars.
I see. Good thing she got treated early.
Yes. It's thanks to your heroics.
Thank you for the meal!
What's this?
That's my treat.
Appreciate it!
Hey! Delicious!
Mister, I bet you'd really thrive
if you set up shop in Ueno!
What do you know about it?
Mister, how's business these days?
How's it look to you?
Sorry.
THE SLASHER APPEARS AGAIN
TRAIN CONDUCTOR'S BODY
WAS FOUND IN TRAIN
BRUTALLY MURDERED
Thanks to all the talk about
that Slasher being at large around here,
people just stopped coming out at night.
POSSIBILITY OF USING TRAINS
FOR TRANSPORTATION
I even had to let my workers go.
They say that a conductor got killed
the other day.
On top of that, do you know that
the Mugen Train is out of service now?
Rumor has it...
that around 40 of its passengers
just disappeared without a trace.
Oh... It sounds ominous.
Flame Hashira,
getting back to why I'm here...
We've located the Mugen Train.
MUGEN
We've received word that it was secretly
transported to a certain train shed.
Is that right?
Delicious!
Will we be heading to the Mugen Train?
Right.
But first...
let's inspect the station
where the conductor's body was found.
Fuku, enough of that sighing.
Go on and eat your bean paste bun.
Yeah.
Not many customers today again, right?
I know that I say this every day,
but it's dangerous to be out after dark.
Tomorrow, you can start
helping out in the afternoon.
Since the demons come out at night.
All clear!
I took a look around the area,
but there was nothing amiss.
Right!
There aren't any demons!
You're bringing up demons again?
Just stop, will you?
I have to sell as many bento as I can!
It's hard enough
with my mother being pregnant,
and I heard that
my father's shop isn't doing well.
HOW TO COOK WESTERN FOOD
You can leave that kind
of worrying to us adults.
I'll take care of things in the early mornings
and nighttime by myself, okay?
And what are we going to do
if you get attacked by the Slasher, too?
BEEF NABE BENTO
REGULAR BENTO
I would be more than happy
to sacrifice my life for yours.
Grandma!
Well, good evening!
The moon is exquisite tonight, is it not?
I'm searching for a demon.
You haven't seen one, have you?
What? Just like that?
Lord Kyojuro!
You're being far too blunt!
Ma'am, is there something
you can tell me?
D-Demon? What kind of talk is that?
Wh-What's wrong with you?
Stay away from us!
Look out!
If you keep shaking like that,
you'll end up dropping
your precious bean paste bun!
Stay away from me!
Delicious!
I don't believe in demons!
There's no way there could be any,
and you know it!
Fuku, that's enough.
I don't believe this man is a bad person.
I'm sorry. I feel like I'm always on edge
these days because of the Slasher incidents.
If what I was just told is correct,
you two start working while it's still dark out
and come to sell us those bento.
I couldn't be more thankful.
No one should ever hurt people like you.
But you can rest easy now!
I'll take care of the Slasher!
Who in the world are you?
All right, then!
Excuse me!
Um... If you don't mind,
could you maybe buy some bento?
That's a good idea!
Okay!
I'll buy them all!
Excuse me, Flame Hashira...
That'll make a splendid gift
for the other Corps members!
I'll be going on alone now.
Thanks for your hard work.
Goodbye.
What was that all about?
I'm glad he bought all those bento, but...
Let's hurry home now, Fuku.
I'm getting a really bad feeling.
I can feel a chill going down my spine.
Grandma?
Who...
Who are you?
I'm a bento vendor as you can see!
I am in no way suspicious!
But this train is heading to the shed now.
Right! I'm aware of that.
I heard that's where
I can find the Mugen Train.
That's the one I have business with.
The Mugen Train?
If that's the one you're looking for,
it's no longer in the shed.
Is that right?
It was transported to a well-equipped
maintenance facility this morning.
That one over there.
Ah.
All right, then this is
where I'm getting off!
What?
What do you mean, "get off"?
Hey!
DEMON SLAYER: KIMETSU NO YAIBA
MUGEN TRAIN ARC
The Mugen Train...
I see.
Though faint, the trace of a demon remains.
MUGEN
Hey you!
This place is off-limits!
Hey!
I was sent here by the Railway Bureau
to deliver these bento.
Oh?
Hey! He says he brought us bento!
Hey, take one to Tatsu.
He's resting in the office.
Yes, sir.
Why was the Mugen Train brought here?
Right, when there's no way
it's a problem with the body.
Word on the street
is that it's a man-eating train.
You don't know how bitter that makes us.
So now that it's being put
back into service,
we want to do all we can to get her back into shape
and send her back out into the world.
Back into service?
Yeah, tomorrow night.
That's why we're all here—
Demon!
There's a demon here!
Oh!
Tatsu!
All of you, step back!
Chief!
You bastard...
Let the boy go!
A Demon Slayer? How arrogant.
Ugh! What's this stench?
Ever since I became a demon,
I can't stand human food. It's so disgusting.
That bento was made with love
by people I know.
I can't just ignore that.
If it's revolting, it's revolting.
Hey boy, your blood smells
like it might be revolting, too.
I'll just devour the humans that seem tasty,
but the ones that taste bad...
I like to show myself a good time
by tormenting them all night!
So, that's what this is about, Slasher?
I find you offensive.
If you don't like me, then...
let's see you slash me!
Wha...
What's going on?
No one's ever been able to stop me.
I'm the fastest...
of them all!
Hey, sorry about that.
You can't bring yourself to slash me
with this kid in my arms.
Should I be considerate
and just kill him off?
H-Help...
Help me!
Don't worry!
I'm going to save you, no matter what!
Not on your life. Just yesterday...
I slashed this other woman
until I was sick of doing it.
I see. Now I know how fast you are.
But I wouldn't get cocky if I were you.
Last night, we thought
you'd fled because we showed up,
but apparently, you never even detected us.
It's true that you're quick to escape at least!
What?
We were able to treat your victim
from last night right away.
She'll recover without even a single scar.
Even if she does survive, she's doomed
to be consumed by fear for the rest of her life.
I won't let that happen!
We're going to treat
the wounds of her soul,
no matter how hard it may be to heal them,
for as long as it takes!
I'll show that self-righteous
face of yours a thing or two.
I'm going to go kill that woman again!
We're keeping her hidden!
You'll never find her!
All right, then those bento vendors...
They have nothing to do with me!
But you know them, right?
Those are station bento, right?
I can find out where they're from.
Don't move!
You do offend me, you know.
Well, I'm enjoying this!
If you want to save them,
then get to the station before me.
Before that happens...
I'll have to kill this one!
I'll be going on ahead.
Please...
Please save him!
It'll be okay. Just leave it to me.
Also, my friends will be coming soon.
This way! This way! This way!
Lord Rengoku!
Where's the medical squad?
They're on their way.
I've given him first aid.
I'm leaving the rest to you.
Total Concentration Breathing.
Really, you don't listen, do you?
If I say I'm going to help,
then I'm going to help!
Good morning!
Hey! You're as early as ever!
I can smell them!
All right!
Station Master?
It smells. It smells!
It's you, isn't it?
The one who's got the stink
of those bento clinging to her!
Don't take this personally.
It's all that Demon Slayer's fault!
Make a run for it, Fuku!
What's the big idea, you hag?
Y-You're...
You're not hurt, are you?
Grandma!
Damn!
Hey, old hag...
You're going to wish you hadn't...
How the hell...
did you catch up to me?
I thought I told you not to get cocky.
Why don't we see who's faster?
Whether I can slash
this old hag's throat first
or you can claim my head first!
No need to put it to the test.
You're...
slow!
Flame Breathing...
First Form...
Unknowing Fire!
You...
saved us, didn't you?
Twice.
Grandma...
I'll never forget that face, that haori.
Fuku's mother...
and I...
20 years ago, you saved our lives.
Grandma, what are you talking about?
That must've been my father.
I'm following in my father's footsteps,
slaying demons.
I'm honored to have protected you
just as my father did.
I still can't believe it!
I'm sorry for saying that
there couldn't be any demons, Grandma.
No! That's how it should be!
Not knowing about demons,
never running into one...
There's no better way to live out your life!
Flame Hashira! Are you all right?
I only just took care of it now.
Thank you for a job well done!
Right!
So, what about the Mugen Train?
The maintenance work
will be done tonight,
and it's going back into service tomorrow.
I'm glad to hear that!
So all's well that ends well, right?
It's a little too soon to be saying that.
A demon who's devoured more than 40 people
is surely on a different level than this one.
Then, the Slasher was only here
to serve as a distraction?
That might very well be true.
Either way, there's a different demon
on the Mugen Train.
A demon who's far more powerful
and mysterious is lurking somewhere.
Tomorrow, to the Mugen Train, then.
Needless to say, I'll be boarding it!
Actually, it's today now!
Hey, Pops, did you hear?
Huh?
They say that the Mugen Train
is back in service.
MUGEN TRAIN
TO RESUME OPERATION
Oh?
I just hope nothing odd happens again.
Excuse me!
Hey there, bento vendor!
I don't know what to say
to thank you for this morning.
Please take these.
This is all that we have to give you.
Ah! The thing is,
I missed out on having one last night!
Nothing could make me happier!
But I will pay for it.
No, it's the thought
that counts!
Is that right?
Then let me accept this one
and buy all the rest that you have there!
Whaaaaat?
Please be careful.
Please stop by again
if you're in the area!
I promise to tell my father about you two.
I'm sure he'll be thrilled.
Now then, take care!
Let's meet again one day!
Wha...
Wh-What...
What the hell is this creature?
Here's your first-class bento!
That will be 36 sen, please!
Would you like some tea
or sake with that?
Comin' through!
Stop it! You're embarrassing us!
What's going on?
Now then, let me partake of this
with gratitude!
Delicious!
So, we were able
to board the Mugen Train!
Tanjiro, isn't there something
you want to ask the Flame Hashira?
I hope we get to meet him!
Yeah!
Hashira, huh? Fight me!
Stop that yammering!
Just shut up!
What did you say?
You have a problem with that?
Okay, we hear you, Inosuke!
Calm down now!
You idiot boar!
Anyway, I wonder what kind of person
the Flame Hashira is.
Well—
It's the Kasugai Crow!
It seems like the Kasugai Crow
has looked into Rengoku for us.
What? Really?
He says he found out
how the other Hashira feel about Rengoku.
That I have to hear!
Hashira! All of you, fight me!
All right. Tanjiro, let's hear it.
Okay. Then, let me start
with Lady Shinobu.
HOW THE INSECT HASHIRA
SHINOBU KOCHO
SEES RENGOKU
I'd say he's a good person.
Though there are times
when we're not on the same wavelength.
Lady Shinobu!
You remind me of that good smell!
How about the other Hashira?
Okay, let's hear them all in one go!
ACCORDING TO TENGEN UZUI
Flamboyant!
Sticks out even more than me.
But he's a really great guy!
ACCORDING TO
MUICHIRO TOKITO
He's like an owl.
That cheery voice
is so comforting to hear.
ACCORDING TO
MITSURI KANROJI
He's a super-cool big brother!
I had so much fun
training with him!
He really doted on me!
ACCORDING TO
OBANAI IGURO
Talks a lot.
Has a good personality.
LOVE HIM
ACCORDING TO
SANEMI SHINAZUGAWA
He's a good guy.
LOVE HIM
ACCORDING TO GYOMEI HIMEJIMA
Positive.
Never whines.
Honest.
So, something like that.
Wait, what about Tomioka?
He's right, Kasugai Crow.
What about Tomioka?
I see.
This is what Tomioka had to say about Rengoku...
ACCORDING TO GIYU TOMIOKA
He often speaks to me.
LOVE HIM
And there you have it!
Oh, really? It seems like everyone
loves the Flame Hashira, huh?
Yeah. I can't wait to meet him!
Flame Hashira! Fight me!
Inosuke!
Rengoku!
Next, Demon Slayer: Kimetsu no Yaiba
Mugen Train Arc, Episode 2, "Deep Sleep"!
Let's all board the train together!
Big Bro!
TO BE CONTINUED