UPPER SIX
Please work!
Just for a second!
That way...
DESTROY
someone can behead him for sure!
DESTROYER
OF DEMONS
EPISODE 9:
DEFEATING AN UPPER RANK DEMON
UZUI FAMILY GRAVE
If my siblings were still alive...
maybe we would've gone drinking one day.
Sorry,
but I still haven't managed to die yet.
But I did bring some fine sake,
so cut me some slack.
One day,
we'll all drink together over there.
Now, in their honor,
dig in and be as flashy as you can!
Whoa, these are tasty!
Don't hold back, you three.
Lord Tengen, do you...
Huh?
Lord Tengen, do you still think
about your deceased siblings?
Sure.
Not a day goes by
that I don't recall them.
Even now, it seems like yesterday
that I left my homeland with you three.
Hey, this one's tasty, too!
Come on, join me!
Right.
Delicious!
Hey! Would it kill you
to show some restraint?
Now, now...
But Lord Tengen told us to dig in!
Here you go, Makio!
Delicious.
Isn't it?
Someday, I'm going to Hell.
Oh...
Whoops!
I shouldn't have said that!
I don't need another tongue-lashing
from you three.
I'm going to live the flashiest life possible.
For my siblings' sake.
With you three, that is.
Right.
How lovely.
Th-Thank you very much.
Sure.
Lord Tengen! Lord Tengen!
Me, too! Me, too!
You plastered them
on yourself, didn't you?
You're so cruel, Lord Tengen!
Lord Tengen, would you mind
giving me that petal?
I don't mind at all,
but there are tons of them everywhere.
That's the one that I want.
Thank you very much.
- Lord Tengen, I want one, too!
Huh?
Just pick up one of these petals yourselves!
- You're so cruel!
Lord Tengen!
He regenerated his legs?
Dammit! He's already neutralized the poison!
Man, that sure packed a punch!
This poison, I mean!
Blood Demon Art...
Rotating Circular Slashes...
Flying Blood Scythes!
Slashing us without even swinging his arms?
Over a wide range!
Sound Breathing...
Fourth Form...
Constant Resounding Slashes!
He vanished?
Lord Tengen, behind you!
Hinatsu—
I'll draw the Belts toward myself!
Lord Tengen, don't mind me!
Go look for the dem—
Well, you have a lot of nerve.
I'm sure going to mind you, you hear me?
Hinatsuru!
Dammit!
The Belts are blocking me!
Hinatsuru!
Wow!
It's so beautiful here,
isn't it, Lord Tengen?
I wish I could become a dragonfly
and soar like that!
Hey, that's a flashy dream
if I ever heard one!
There you go again, sounding like a fool!
For heaven's sake!
What? That's so not true!
I hate you, Makio!
What was that?
I dare you to say that again!
Lord Tengen...
After defeating an Upper Rank demon...
let's withdraw from the front lines...
and live as ordinary people.
Though we were raised as shinobi,
and though it won't bring back
the lives that we took...
we still need to set things right
somewhere along the line...
or else we can never hold our heads up
as long as we live.
When that day comes,
all four of us might not be alive.
But no hard feelings, all right?
Leave her alone!
Move!
Move, move, move!
Another person's about to be killed! Another
person's about to be killed before my eyes!
Close the distance! Jump!
Up on the roof!
You can't always be the one
under protection!
Try to be even a little bit useful!
He doesn't see me as a threat!
That's because I'm weak!
If I make an unpredictable move,
I can save her!
Use the kagura!
Hinokami Kagura's the answer!
I can reach her easy with that!
It's no good! I have no stamina!
I can't dig in!
What should I do? Hurry! Hurry!
What am I going to do?
Think! Think!
What's the most that I can do?
What is it that I can do right now?
Seriously, that was a lightning-fast move.
There's no way
he can still move like that!
I did it! I did it!
Blend the breathing techniques!
Use Water Breathing
and the Hinokami Kagura in combination!
That'll give me more attack power
than I'd have with just Water Breathing,
and I'll also be able to move longer
than with just the Hinokami Kagura!
I'm sure the swordsmen who've fought
the demons until now did just that.
Taking the breathing techniques
and sword skills that suited them best,
and modifying them into the form
that would allow them to exert maximum power!
Because they racked their brains!
That's why so many different offshoots
have been created!
Modify it...
into any form.
Be flexible!
That's the fighting style
that Urokodaki taught me!
Even if I can never fully master
Water Breathing like Tomioka has,
I won't let what Urokodaki taught me...
go to waste!
Either way, you're going down!
Tanjiro Kamado!
You have my gratitude!
DEMON SLAYER: KIMETSU NO YAIBA
ENTERTAINMENT DISTRICT ARC
UPPER SIX
Dammit!
These things are flapping around
like crazy! So annoying!
Dammit! They're slithery,
but they're freaking hard!
They just keep coming!
Huh?
Dammit!
They're about to decapitate him!
Inosuke! Here comes
the next assault!
Crap! We can't bring this one down
unless we strike in tandem!
We're stirring things up as we flee,
so we're able to dodge her attacks somehow,
but there's no point in just dodging!
We have to close the distance...
and go for her head!
Inosuke! Calm down!
There's absolutely no reason for us
to slash them at the same time!
We just need to make sure
the two demons' heads aren't connected!
Even after they behead their demon,
don't give up! Let's unleash our attack!
You...
Look at you!
Damn! You really are something else!
What's wrong?
Stay alert! Go for his head yourself!
I can do this!
Damn!
Won't budge!
The likes of you, cut off my head?
Never going to happen!
My blade's stuck!
Don't swing your head
all the way behind you!
Damn you!
Not that again!
Kamado! Hang on!
Uzui!
Lord Tengen!
Uzui—
Look out!
Inosuke! Zenitsu!
They're forcing us to change our strategy!
Muscle!
I can't close in on that worm woman,
no matter what!
So the three of us will take her on while the old guy
deals with the praying mantis demon alone!
At least this one's weaker
than the man with the scythe!
Let's decapitate this one first!
Tanjiro, can you still move?
I can move!
But Uzui's been poisoned by the enemy,
so he's in bad shape!
We have to finish this
as soon as possible!
That was close! I barely blocked it!
He's attacking us even as he fights Uzui?
Hinatsuru!
Don't worry about me!
I'll go hide! Just focus on winning!
Look out! Behind you!
Are you all right?
Yes! Thank you!
I can see that your movements
are getting more and more sluggish!
I wonder which of you
will be the first to fall apart!
Dammit! Monichi and I
are practically unscathed!
We gotta take care of this!
The other two are all banged up!
What was the point of all that training?
What was the point?
Inosuke!
This demon's neck is too soft to slash!
It's going to take a lot of speed!
We'll have to slash her
from multiple directions, or it won't work!
Now that it's heading
toward Tanjiro, as well,
it seems like the attack's slightly...
ever so slightly slowed down!
It looks that way to me!
I'm just going to assume that it has!
All right!
If it's multiple directions you want,
just leave it to yours truly,
the dual-wielder, dammit!
The three of us together...
can beat her!
Gotcha!
Zenitsu, we're protecting Inosuke!
Okay!
Even if you bring
another ugly freak into the fray,
it's not going to change anything!
Inosuke!
Let's go!
Don't be late, my underlings!
Beast Breathing...
Eighth Fang...
Explosive...
Rush!
Water Breathing...
Third Form!
Thunder Breathing...
First Form...
Flowing...
Thunderclap and Flash!
...Dance!
Eightfold!
He's...
He's only focusing on heading
straight toward me without any defense!
I'm getting it done this time!
You can't cut if off!
There's no way you can cut it off!
Not with these beat-up blades!
Sixth Fang...
Palisade Bite!
You did it, Inosuke!
Amazing! You used them like saws
to behead her!
Hah!
Her head! Her head! Her head!
I'm gonna race off with it somewhere
far away so she can't stick it back on!
For now, I'm gonna run
all over the place with this head, okay?
You two go help the old guy!
Gotcha!
Be careful, Inosuke!
Sure thing!
Uzui!
We have to join him right away!
You damn boar! You let me go!
Your attacks are pretty lame!
What did you say?
Maybe you can't die, but it sure looks
like you get weak once your head's cut off!
Inosuke!
Inosuke! Inosuke!
This is bad! The poison!
Where's the wound?
Was he stabbed in the heart?
It's so dark, I can't see!
Dammit! Dammit!
What's he doing here?
Where's Uzui?
Uzui!
Tanjiro! Look out!
Oh, damn!
Zenitsu...
Forget about me!
This happened
because I wasn't paying attention!
I'm sorry, Inosuke!
If only I'd noticed him sooner!
No... I...
If I hadn't left Uzui's side in the first place,
this wouldn't have happened!
Sorry.
Sorry!
Sorry, everyone!
Sorry...
Nezuko.
NIN-NIN
Nin-nin!
Beast Breathing, Eighth Fang...
Explosive Rush!
Thunder Breathing, First Form...
Thunderclap and Flash! Eightfold!
Water Breathing, Third Form...
Flowing Dance!
Inosuke!
Zenitsu!
Uzui!
We still can't win?
Don't give up!
Don't give up! Don't give up!
Next, Episode 10, "Never Give Up"!
TO BE CONTINUED