TOKITO HOUSE
Oiran! Oiran!
Let's play! Let's play!
Fine, fine.
Oiran!
Read me a story!
VERY YOUNG
CHILDREN
I'll be happy to.
Which should I read?
YOUNG
LADY
Hmm, let's see.
Me, too!
YOUNG
LADY
Read me a story, too!
All right, then let me read this one first,
and when I'm done, shall I read that one?
You can read mine later!
Mine, too!
You always copy me!
Well, because—
Now, now...
Oh, that reminds me!
First, l have something to give to you two.
What is it? What is it?
What are you giving us, Oiran?
But...
these are your treasures,
aren't they, Oiran?
It's okay. Don't you worry.
I want to give them to you
because I'm fond of you both.
- Thank you!
Oiran! Oiran! Put this comb on me!
Now! Now!
Right. One at a time, okay?
EPISODE 4:
TONIGHT
Nowhere to be found?
Yes. Uh, it's Zenko.
The one with the yellow hair.
She'd fainted, so we put her to bed,
but she's not in her room.
Shall I have them look for her?
Don't bother.
Forget it. Don't look for her.
It's Ashinuke! What do I care!
She must've run off somewhere.
Just forget about it.
But Master...
Would you shut the hell up?
Dismissed!
Don't ever mention Zenko's name again!
Tell the others not to, either.
It's all because they got
on Warabihime Oiran's nerves!
Both Zenko and Omitsu.
I... told... you!
There's a demon at my House, all right?
Well...
I'm telling you, it was a thing like this!
You know, like this!
Yeah, sure, uh...
Hold up a second, okay?
Like this?
Do you get this, then?
Uzui and Zenitsu should be
coming soon to check in, so—
It was like this, okay?
It was clear to me!
Yeah. Yeah.
Zenitsu won't be coming.
This guy's got mad skills!
He didn't make a sound.
Not even the slightest puff of wind!
"Zenitsu won't be coming."
What do you mean by that?
I feel bad about putting you through this.
I wanted to...
rescue my wives so badly,
I made some bad decisions.
As it stands, Zenitsu is missing.
There's been no contact since last night.
You two should leave now.
You're ranked too low for this.
If the demon here turns out to be
an Upper Rank, you couldn't handle it.
If you vanish from here,
they'll assume that you're dead.
I'll be continuing this mission on my own.
No, Uzui, we—
Don't be ashamed!
Whoever survives, wins.
Don't overlook your chance.
Come back here, old man!
You think he can't trust us
because we're the lowest ranked?
Hey, our rank is Kanoe.
We've already moved up.
Huh?
Do you remember all the rankings?
KANAO
KINOE
KINOTO
HINOE
HINOTO
TSUCHINOE
TSUCHINOTO
KANOE
KANOTO
MIZUNOE
MIZUNOTO
USED TO BE HERE
Remember how we used to be Mizunoto
at the very bottom?
Now we're fourth from the bottom, Kanoe!
KANAO
NOW WE'RE HERE!!
Oh snap! You caught up to me!
Eat it, you pissant crybaby!
We'll be moving past you in no time!
What was that, you stupid boar?
You wanna fight?
HEADS
Ready? Watch this.
Show me my ranking.
KANOE
How do you like that?
What was that?
Huh? They fiddled with your arm
at the Wisteria Mountain, didn't they?
I remember them fiddling with it,
but I was exhausted.
It's called "Wisteria Flower Engraving," and you say
that phrase and flex your muscles to invoke it.
I had no idea about that.
It's a sign that you're a Demon Slayer.
Hey, cheer up!
Wait! We don't have time for this! Sorry!
As soon as night falls,
I'll head over to your Ogimoto House!
OGIMOTO HOUSE
So wait for me until then.
It'd be dangerous to make a move on your own!
Why should I do that?
I'll be done investigating
my own House today!
I told you, the demon's at my House,
so you'd better come with me now!
How stupid are you, anyway?
For crying out loud!
Would they just shut up?
That's not what I meant!
Uzui was patrolling outside the Houses
during the night, right?
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Even still, Zenitsu disappeared!
And the demon at your place
is nowhere to be seen right now!
Hey! Could you stop smacking me around?
I think there must be a passageway
inside the building!
Passageway?
That's right. And since
it's not coming in and out...
there's a good chance
that the demon is working on the inside.
If the demon's working in the House...
and cleverly disguising itself as a human...
then it'd be all the more careful about killing people
to make sure that its cover won't be blown.
I get it.
Cleaning up after a murder
would be a hassle.
And wiping away bloodstains
would be a chore.
This is a nightlife district.
It can be convenient for demons in more ways
than one, but also just as inconvenient for them.
They have to work at night.
It would seem suspicious
if they weren't around.
You're right.
I think that not only Zenitsu,
but Uzui's wives, as well, are all still alive!
I'm going to take action with that in mind.
I'm going to rescue them, no matter what!
I want you to take action
with that in mind, too.
And no matter what...
I don't want you to die.
Are you okay with that?
Everything you just said...
is what I was about to say myself!
Oiran...
We've brought you your tea.
Thank you. I can do the rest myself,
so go on and have your dinner.
All right!
- We'll be going on ahead, then!
- Pardon us!
I love you, Koinatsu Oiran!
I love you, too!
Yes! I love you right back!
Now that we're clear, go on, okay?
- Right!
Didn't Oiran look really happy?
Didn't she?
Oh, those girls...
Miss Koinatsu?
Sumi?
Forgive me for being so rude.
I am leaving the Tokito House.
Could you please give Master
my payment for my food and lodging?
Sumi...
The way you're dressed...
I had to dress as a woman
for certain reasons,
but I'm actually a guy!
Oh, I already knew that.
It was obvious at a glance.
And your voice...
What?
I knew you were a boy from the start.
I did wonder what you were up to, but...
Who knew that I was busted?
You have your reasons, don't you?
You were worried about Suma
for real, weren't you?
Yes! That's the truth! That was no lie!
I promise you
I'll rescue everyone who vanished!
Thank you.
That sets my mind at ease a bit.
You see, I'm leaving
this district tomorrow.
Is that right?
You must be so happy!
There's someone who would want
even me as his wife.
I really couldn't be happier right now!
But...
that's all the more reason why I was worried sick
about those I'm leaving behind.
Even if I were to get a bad feeling
about something,
I have no way of even looking into it.
No one can blame you for that.
Please don't worry about it.
Please always keep a smile on your face.
I don't want you to disappear, either...
Sumi.
Now then, I'll be off.
I wish you every happiness.
Thank you.
You, too, Sumi.
And I'm counting on you to save Suma.
Right!
Did you forget something?
That's right.
I need to devour you before I forget.
UPPER SIX
Since tonight's your last night here.
Right, Koinatsu?
Not good!
The sun's almost set completely!
I gotta get to Inosuke's place fast!
There's a scent.
A sweet smell. It's faint.
It's a demon!
It's the scent of a demon!
It's nearby!
No way!
DEMON SLAYER: KIMETSU NO YAIBA
ENTERTAINMENT DISTRICT ARC
Late!
It's almost nightfall,
and he's not here yet!
Souichiro, you moron!
I'm gonna take action...
with the spirit of "Comin' through!"
in my heart!
Hey, mice! My swords!
That guy has mad skills.
Muscle! Muscle!
Muscle!
Setting me up with these
"Muscular Mice" subordinates!
I wanna boss around some Ninju, too!
- Muscle!
- Muscle! Muscle!
Let's go slay some demons!
Comin'...
through!
What happened to Zenko and Hinatsuru?
Give me the short version.
No questions from you, got that?
Zenko's disappeared.
Hinatsuru fell ill and left for the Kirimise.
Tell me everything
that you think might be relevant.
Who are you suspecting?
You can trust me, so speak up.
I'll kill whoever it is if it's the last thing I do.
I'll get revenge for you.
Omitsu...
An Oiran named Warabihime.
She's in a room on the north side
that has no light.
Not here.
She must be on the prowl for humans.
I'll head to where Hinatsuru is
as I try to pinpoint the demon's presence.
If she's still alive,
she should have some information for me.
Either way, the demon should be
back here by daybreak.
I'll dispose of it with my own two hands!
The scent is strong!
There's no question!
Miss Koinatsu!
Are you a Demon Slayer?
So you came.
How many of you are there?
I know one is that yellow-haired,
ugly little brat.
Is there a Hashira with you?
Or will he be here soon?
I know you're not a Hashira.
You seem weak, after all.
I have no use for anyone
who's not a Hashira.
Got that?
Her body...
What's going on?
I don't see Miss Koinatsu's body.
She's not bleeding.
There's no scent of blood!
I never devour dirty old people or anyone ugly.
UPPER SIX
Upper...
Six!
Let that person go!
Who do you think you're talking to?
How dare you...
She's so fast!
I never saw that coming!
Upper Rank...
I have no strength in my limbs.
My body's numb!
Calm down!
My body's responding fine.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be alive right now!
I have no strength in my limbs...
because I'm afraid!
My body's numb because I hit
my back hard, so no wonder!
That demon's weapon is her Belt!
It has supernatural abilities!
She can absorb humans inside it!
That's why no matter how hard
I searched inside the building,
I couldn't find a secret path
that a human could fit through!
All she needs to abduct humans
is a crack big enough for that Belt!
Oh, you're still alive?
You're not as fragile as I thought.
I do like your eyes. They're lovely.
I'll just gouge out your eyeballs
and devour them.
The box!
It's not broken.
But the next time she attacks me,
it's sure to be destroyed!
Sorry, Nezuko.
The shoulder strap broke.
I can't carry you while I fight!
Don't you leave that box.
Unless your life is in danger.
Water Breathing...
Fourth Form!
Striking Tide... Turbulent!
Your midair moves weren't half bad.
Also...
you certainly did a fine job separating her.
Right where I'd trapped Koinatsu.
I mean, how cute is that?
As ugly as you are!
I'm starting to get rather fond of you.
You're like a rat on the brink of death.
Upper Six.
Can I do it?
Without Uzui, Zenitsu or Inosuke...
Can I take on an Upper Rank alone?
No.
It's not a matter of if I can do it!
I have to do it!
NIN-NIN
Nin-nin!
Thanks for your hard work, you three!
Muscle!
Who the heck are these guys?
They're Ninju.
The Muscular Mice!
They go into cramped spaces
where we wouldn't fit...
Muscle!
...and help slay demons behind the scenes.
Muscle! Muscle!
You could say they are
the Shadow Demon Slayer Corps.
And now, time for a Taisho-era secret!
We took care to assemble only the most
dedicated mice to train as the Muscular Mice,
but being narcissistic enough to fall in love
with their own muscles is also a must.
In other words, they have to have
a flair for flashiness.
Next, Episode 5,
"Things Are Gonna Get Real Flashy!!"
Muscle!
TO BE CONTINUED
These guys have mad skills.