Tanjiro...
Take up your sword.
There's something you must cut.
There's something...
I must cut.
There's something I must cut...
in order to wake up.
I think I know what it is.
Don't hesitate! Do it!
You have to do it!
My death in this dream
will lead me to reality!
In other words...
what I have to cut is...
my own neck!
You must be the incarnations
of this boy's soul.
The air is so clear, and it feels good.
Is that his spiritual core?
Why are you showing it to me?
Did you bring me here
because I was searching for it?
No way!
Even though I was trying to destroy it?
Why would you...
EPISODE 4:
INSULT
Where the heck is his spiritual core?
What's with this realm
of the subconscious?
And that creepy naked boar...
Seriously, this is insane.
What are you doing
in the realm of the subconscious?
You stupid naked boar!
It's pitch-dark.
It's pitch-dark,
and I can't see a thing. Dammit.
What's with that blond brat's
realm of subconscious?
Do I have to grope around
to find his spiritual core?
You must be kidding me.
What was that?
What the hell's a guy doing in here?
Damn you, parasite!
No one's allowed in here but Nezuko.
I'm so going to kill you.
Where's Nezuko?
Wh-Who the heck knows?
All right, then... Die!
Nooo!
Wake up...
I have to wake up...
Hurry!
Nezuko!
I'm all right. I'm alive.
Nezuko! Are you okay?
Nezuko...
Zenitsu...
Inosuke...
Rengoku...
Who are these people?
They're all connected
by the wrists with ropes.
Rope...
What's this?
It's burned off.
Nezuko's burning blood did it?
It's faint, but I'm picking up
a demon's scent, too!
This smell... The ticket!
I knew it. It's giving off
a faint demon smell, too.
TOKYO - MUGEN
We were put to sleep
when our tickets were punched.
This must be a demon's work!
Did he unleash such a potent Blood Demon Art
using just this faint scent?
I don't know why...
but I have a feeling that I shouldn't sever
this rope with my Nichirin Sword.
Nezuko! Do me a favor!
I want you to burn off everyone's rope!
Zenitsu! Wake up!
Wake up, Zenitsu!
You have to wake up!
Wake up, Inosuke! Please!
Inosuke...
There, there... Sorry, okay?
Thanks.
You did a great job, Nezuko.
It's no good. These two won't wake up.
What can I do?
Rengoku—
What are you doing?
Is a demon controlling her?
Get out of our way!
Thanks to you guys,
we won't be able to have dreams!
Is she acting of her own free will?
This man, too?
What do you think you're doing?
If you're awake,
you'd better help us out!
You may have tuberculosis or whatever,
but if you don't do your job,
I'm going to tell him, and then,
he won't show you any dreams, you hear me?
Is he the one
who was connected to me?
Tuberculosis...
He's sick.
Poor man.
What this demon did is unforgivable.
He took advantage of their weak souls!
Sorry.
I have to go fight.
You want to stay
inside a happy dream, don't you?
I know.
I wanted to stay inside my dream, too.
If only this was the dream...
Until I touched his heart...
I was willing to hurt others...
if it meant I could escape
from the pain of this illness.
But now...
Are you all right?
Thank you.
Be careful.
Right!
Nezuko!
The smell is overpowering!
So heavy!
The demon's scent is so strong
even in this strong wind!
Was I asleep in such an awful scent?
Even if each car was closed off and airtight,
I can't believe I was!
I was useless!
The demon's upwind...
Is he in the first car?
Nezuko, don't come!
Stay away from me and wait!
Go wake everyone up!
What? You're awake?
Good morning!
You could've stayed asleep.
DREAM
LOWER ONE
It was him!
DEMON SLAYER: KIMETSU NO YAIBA
MUGEN TRAIN ARC
Why did you wake up?
Didn't I show you a sweet dream?
I could've shown you a dream
where your family was being slaughtered.
Would you have liked that one better?
No, of course not.
Too distressing, right?
All right, next...
Why don't I show you a dream
where your father comes back to life?
What I really love...
is to show people nightmares
right after a happy dream.
I just adore the sight
of a distorted human face.
I get such a kick out of that!
How enthralling is it to gaze at someone
shattered by misfortune, suffering and flailing?
But I don't usually let my guard down.
So, it may take longer,
but I'll make sure to kill the Demon Slayers.
I mixed my blood
with the ink on the tickets.
Once the conductor punches them,
creating clamp marks...
the spell activates.
This is a remote art.
It took more effort, but this was
the best way to avoid being detected.
Not being detected is important.
It is reality for them
until they realize it's a dream.
And yet...
how did this one manage to wake up?
And he found the way to wake up in a short time.
Even though the human desire for blissful dreams,
for self-serving dreams...
is so enormous!
Don't you dare intrude on my soul!
I won't let you...
get away with this!
What's that? I see he's wearing earrings.
How lucky is that?
So, he came right to me!
This is like a dream!
Now I can receive
even more blood of Master Muzan!
And once I become more powerful,
I'll challenge an Upper Rank demon
to a duel to replace him!
Water Breathing...
Tenth Form...
Constant Flux!
Blood Demon Art!
Whispers of Forced Unconscious Hypnosis.
Go to sleep!
He's not falling asleep.
Go to sleep.
Go to sleep!
Go... to... sleep!
It's not working. But why not?
No, that's not what this is.
He's falling under this spell over and over!
He's aware that he's under the spell right away.
And he's committing suicide
in order to awaken!
Even if it's in the middle of a dream,
to commit suicide...
to take his own life with his own hands...
that takes incredible willpower!
This brat...
is insane!
Why didn't you save us?
What were you doing
while we were being murdered?
How could you be the only one to survive?
Why do you think you were here?
You're so useless!
It should've been you that died.
How dare you go on living
without a care?
There's no way they'd ever say that!
Not ever! Not my family!
Don't you dare...
insult...
my family!
It was way too easy.
Could this be a dream, too?
Or was this demon weaker than him?
I can totally see why...
he ordered me to kill you,
the boy with the earrings,
along with the Hashira!
Your very existence is, like...
It couldn't be more irritating, you know!
He's not dying?
Oh, that look on your face is so delightful!
That's the look I've been wanting to see!
You want to know why I'm not dead
after you decapitated me, don't you?
Fine, since I'm feeling so ecstatic right now.
It's so easy
even an infant would understand.
It's because the body over there
was no longer my main body.
Same with this thing
that's talking to you now.
It merely looks like my head, but it's not.
While you were snoozing away...
MUGEN
I fused with this train!
Every inch of this train has become
my blood, my flesh and my bones!
Look at your face.
Are you getting it now?
In other words...
the more than 200 passengers
on this train...
are the food that will strengthen
my body even more...
as well as my hostages.
So, do you think
you can protect them by yourself?
All these people packing this train
from one end to the other...
Can you alone keep me
from devouring them?
What should I do? What should I do?
The most I can protect on my own is two cars!
Any more than that,
and I can't guarantee their safety!
Rengoku! Zenitsu! Inosuke!
This is no time to be sleeping!
Wake up, will you? Please!
Nezuko!
Protect the sleeping passengers!
Follow me, damn minions!
All right!
Explosive Awakening!
Comin' through!
Lord Inosuke's comin' through!
Beast Breathing, Fifth Fang...
Crazy Cutting!
Lord Inosuke Hashibira is comin' through!
Inosuke, I'm so glad you're here!
Of course I came!
I'm the boss, you know!
Now, it's time for a Taisho-era secret!
Inosuke's Kasugai Crow
is named Dongurimaru.
He's always by Inosuke's side,
but he nearly got eaten by him,
so now I hear that he's staying invisible!
Inosuke, I'm really counting on you!
Don't be so bossy!
You're just an underling!
You make me feel so secure
when you're around, Inosuke!
Don't make me feel so warm and fuzzy!
Let's go, Monjiro!
Right!
Next, Episode 5, "Move Forward!"
TO BE CONTINUED