Entertainment District?
You know, that thing!
Know what I mean?
The place where...
Huh? You don't get it?
Listen up!
I am a god!
You three are...
trash!
That's the first thing
you need to pound into your heads!
Drive it in!
You're to turn into dogs if I tell you to!
Arf, arf, arf, arf!
Turn into monkeys if I say so!
Woo-hoo!
Hunch over and rub your hands together,
constantly pander to my every whim
You said it!
and suck up to me
with every fiber of your being!
That's our Lord Uzui all right!
Yep.
And let me repeat!
I am a god!
This guy is crazy!
What are you the god of, specifically?
I don't believe this guy!
Good question!
You have potential!
But it's a stupid question!
What potential?
The God of Flashiness.
I'm the God of Festivals.
What an idiot.
He's the God of Stupidity.
No question about it.
I'm the King of the Mountains!
Nice to meet you...
God of Festivals!
What are you talking about?
You sure are creepy!
No! You two are a close match
for each other! Cringeworthy!
Huh? What did you say?
Back off, Inosuke!
Creepy.
Let me go, Konpochiro!
So, he only has distaste for those
living in the same dimension.
So, there's no time to fool around.
Let's go.
Follow me.
Huh?
He vanished?
Whoa!
So fast! Look how far he's gone!
He's no bigger than a sesame seed now!
So, this is the power
of the God of Festivals.
No, that man is Tengen Uzui, a Hashira.
We have to go after him!
Go after him!
Please be careful!
Safe travels!
EPISODE 2:
INFILTRATING THE ENTERTAINMENT DISTRICT
Listen, you three.
Don't do anything
that'll make you stand out.
Remember that we're only here
to case the joint.
Whatever you do,
don't get out of the carriage.
Hey! Don't do it, Zenitsu!
Inosuke!
Come back here!
Those stinking brats!
Settle down, Inosuke!
Get back here, dammit!
Hey, Yellow Boy! Stay where you are!
This is...
It looks like it's daytime.
This is the Yoshiwara Entertainment District.
Awash in vanity
and desire of men and women.
A town of the night
swirling with love and hate.
Flashy, huh?
What the heck is this?
It's teeming with people!
Comin' through!
What the... Calm down, moron!
DESTROY
Hey! Where did the kid
with the yellow head go?
What?
You there, Yellow Boy!
Why don't you stop by?
We have candy!
Come on! This way!
This place is full of beautiful ladies!
Shut the hell up!
You're too young for this!
Take a good look.
See, this place goes to sleep during the day,
and at night, it sparkles and dazzles.
The ideal place for a demon, am I right?
Women who become Courtesans
are mostly sold here due to poverty and debt.
In return, they're given food,
clothing and lodging,
and if they can climb up the ranks,
a rich man might buy out their contracts.
There are ranks among Courtesans, as well.
The highest-ranked "Oiran" is on a different level.
Beauty is a given, and she's also intelligent
and has mastered every traditional art.
She's the breadwinner, on whom
each house has lavished time and money.
A woman of distinction.
Is that right?
All right, that's enough scouting.
Come on.
WISTERIA
Sorry to impose!
Now listen up.
When you've infiltrated the Entertainment
District, first look for my bride.
I'll be digging for information
on the demons, as well.
This is outrageous!
Huh?
I'll thank you not to mess with us!
How dare you use your subordinates
to personally find a bride for yourself!
Huh? How did you get that idea?
Nope! I'm going to have my say!
Zenitsu!
I'm sure that a screwed-up oddball like you
has no luck with the ladies! However! Even so!
Just because you want a wife,
that's no reason to use Demon Slayers like us!
Are you an idiot? I'm talking about a wife
who's infiltrated the Entertainment District
and is hard at work
gathering intel on the demons!
I've stopped receiving regular check-ins,
so I'm going, too, all right?
I suppose that's what you fantasize.
You damn punk!
These are the letters
sent via the Kasugai Crow.
There's quite a lot of them.
Has she been undercover
for a long time?
Well, I do have three of them. Wives.
Three of them...
Wives?
Th-Three? Why, you... Why, you...
Why would you have three of them?
You've got a problem with that?
Um, in the letters, they keep reminding you
not to stand out when you come.
That's what I told you, remember?
So, what are we going to do, exactly?
Well, of course, disguise yourselves.
As much as I hate it, in a drab way.
All three of my wives
are brilliant ninjas. Kunoichi.
I was sure that this district would be
the perfect place for the demons,
but when I went in as a customer,
I couldn't get anything on them.
So I sent them in
to get closer than a customer ever could.
Since I've already narrowed down
the likeliest houses to three,
you three will search for my wives there
and gather information.
Suma of the Tokito House,
Makio of the Ogimoto House,
and Hinatsuru of the Kyogoku House.
Your wives must be dead,
don't you think?
Pardon me.
I have brought you
the items you asked for.
Thanks.
DEMON SLAYER: KIMETSU NO YAIBA
ENTERTAINMENT DISTRICT ARC
My, my... Now these three are certainly...
quite homely girls, aren't they?
INOKO
SUMIKO
ZENKO
No, I don't think we can...
Isn't there any way you can reconsider?
Under your training, Madam,
I'm sure they'd turn into diamonds.
I'm sorry, but...
Well, I guess taking in one
wouldn't be a problem!
Then, please take one.
Sorry to impose, Madam.
Then, I think we'll take
the one in the middle!
She looks very obedient.
I promise to work as hard as I can!
SUMIKO: EMPLOYED
You guys are beyond hopeless!
I can barely give you away!
I'm not talking to you, all right?
Are you incensed because I made you
disguise yourself as a girl?
You said you'd do anything I asked!
I don't give a damn
about dressing like a girl, moron!
It's that face of yours!
Look at you! You're a stud!
Don't screw with me!
Hey! Over there!
A bunch of people are swarming around!
Oh, that's a procession of Courtesans.
That's Tokito House's Koinatsu Oiran.
The highest-ranking Courtesan
is going off to meet her client.
How flashy is that?
Wife? Is she your wife, by any chance?
Is that knockout your wife?
That's too much!
You've got three of them!
Are they all beautiful like her?
She's not my wife!
She walks so slow.
She'd get killed in a second
in the mountains.
Hey, mister...
I'll be taking this girl
back to my house.
Is that all right?
Hey, so you're...
The Ogimoto House chaperone.
If she's caught the eye of the Ogimoto House,
I couldn't be more thankful.
But what kind of stroke of luck is this?
Oh please, I have a sure eye
for these things.
Take care of yourself, Inoko!
INOKO: EMPLOYED
Oh no! I'm the only leftover!
REJECTED
OGIMOTO HOUSE
What do you think?
Oh my! Unbelievable!
They'd plastered her face in a bizarre way,
but just look at her now that it's off!
What a steal!
Buying such a beauty so cheap!
I'll train her like nobody's business!
I'll make sure she's in more demand than Kyogoku
House's Warabihime or Tokito House's Koinatsu!
Yes, but this girl is actually quite sturdy!
Well, it's better for a girl
to be plump and meaty, right?
I think she's more muscular than plump.
KYOGOKU HOUSE
Oh, that girl can
really play the shamisen!
Yes, she's so dynamic!
Did she join us recently?
She seems to have a good ear.
I was told that she can play the shamisen
or koto after just one listen.
But she sure is ugly.
I'm surprised that she got taken in here.
The man who brought her here
was drop-dead gorgeous, I hear!
Oh my! Was he really?
I wish I could've seen him!
And that chaperone hag
was totally smitten!
You know what? I can tell.
That girl is to rise to the top.
The grittiness to get back at the man
who abandoned her... I can sense it.
A girl like that has a backbone.
I-I see.
You can have her clean the toilets or whatever!
Please, just take her!
Heck, I'd even give her away for free if I had to!
I'm going to make that guy pay!
I swear I'm going to become
the number one Oiran in Yoshiwara!
TOKITO HOUSE
Sumiko? Sumiko?
Yes?
We're so short-staffed now.
Could you carry these up?
Understood!
I'll take them up right now!
Thanks! You're such a hard worker!
After we removed your makeup,
she found the scar on your forehead,
so the madam was seething
with rage yesterday.
Just stop it! It's no use
lashing out at this poor child!
Yes! I'm so glad
they're letting me work here!
Isn't she rather strong?
Strong.
They're saying that Kyogoku House's madam
fell from a window and died.
That's scary. Let's be careful, okay?
A lot of the older girls are leaving
these days, committing Ashinuke.
So scary!
What's Ashinuke?
That's a lot of baggage!
There!
They're all gifts for Koinatsu Oiran.
Sumiko, you don't know?
Ashinuke means to run away from here
without paying off your debts.
It's really bad if you get caught.
Is that right?
Some people do manage
to run off with the man they love.
Right, like the other day, Suma Oiran...
Suma?
That's Uzui's wife.
Um...
Stop spreading those rumors.
After all, nobody knows
if she really did make it out of here.
- Right.
So, you brought
these up for me?
Thank you.
Um, right.
Come here.
Let me give you some candy.
Eat it in secret by yourself, okay?
I want some, too!
Oiran! Oiran!
No. You just had some, remember?
Um, did Suma Oiran commit Ashinuke?
Why would you ask a question like that?
She has her guard up!
I have to find a way
to ask about Miss Suma.
Um...
Candy.
Suma Oiran is my...
She's my...
older sister!
TANJIRO IS SO HONEST THAT HE CAN'T ASSUME
A NORMAL EXPRESSION WHEN HE LIES
What?
So you were sold into the Entertainment
District after your sister?
Y-Yes.
I've been exchanging letters
with my sister all this time,
and I know she wouldn't commit Ashinuke.
Is that right?
True, I couldn't believe
that Suma would commit Ashinuke, either.
She was such a grounded girl.
There were no signs
that she was infatuated with any man.
But they found her diary.
And I hear that she'd written
about committing Ashinuke.
Ashinuke...
How convenient is that for demons?
Even if someone were to vanish,
people would only assume that she'd run away.
The diary was probably forged.
I pray that you're safe.
We're going to rescue you,
no matter what, Miss Suma!
All quiet today, too.
I'm getting a really bad feeling.
It's like being enveloped in smoke.
So adept at becoming invisible...
Could it be that the demon residing here
is an Upper Rank demon?
If that's the case...
we could be in
for an ultra-flashy fight to the death.
So hot! I'm dying to take these off!
Wearing this stupid outfit
blunts my senses like you wouldn't believe!
Oh, Yae! Do you have a minute?
Do you think Makio's all right?
Well, she's shut herself into her room
and won't come out,
and all she said is that she wasn't feeling well,
but she won't go the hospital!
Sooner or later,
the madam's going to drag her out!
I just brought a meal to her.
I only left it outside her door, but...
Makio? That's Uzui's wife.
I finally heard her name mentioned.
Not feeling well?
Like that would stop her from checking in?
That woman came
from that direction, huh?
Guess I'll take a look.
Oh, Inoko!
You'll hurt yourself if you rush like that!
What a quiet girl.
You have a husky voice,
so don't ever say a word!
And you stink at falsetto, so everyone will know
right away that you're a guy. I'm not kidding.
What am I supposed to do, dammit?
Now, then, answer me.
Who were you writing these letters to?
What was your name again?
Oh, that's right. It's Makio.
Answer me, Makio.
NIN-NIN
Nin-nin!
Huh?
It kills me to admit it,
but you're a stunner.
What are you talking about?
Now, it's time for a Taisho-era secret!
In spite of himself, Zenitsu seems
to have taken a shine to the shamisen,
and he's become
quite a skilled player! Huh?
I'm scared to be alone in the house,
so is it okay if I come over?
But I heard that they're really
doting on you over there.
Is that right? Then I'm going to aspire to become
the number one Oiran in Yoshiwara, after all!
MIRROR
What happened?
Next, Episode 3, "What Are You?"
Zenitsu, are you okay?
Zenitsu!
TO BE CONTINUED