EDO - YOSHIWARA
Hey! This all started
ever since you got here, you know!
How many people do you think
have vanished from this House?
What is it that you're doing on the sly?
EPISODE 3:
WHAT ARE YOU?
TOKYO - YOSHIWARA
So, this is it. Ogimoto House.
ENTERTAINMENT DISTRICT - OGIMOTO HOUSE
Now then, answer me.
Who were you writing these letters to?
What was your name again?
Oh, that's right. It's Makio.
Answer me...
Makio.
ENTERTAINMENT DISTRICT - KYOGOKU HOUSE
It seems like I lost sight of who I was.
I'm supposed to be looking
for Uzui's wife, Hinatsuru.
What good would it do
to hone my shamisen and koto skills?
Still, what am I going to do?
I've been all ears since I got here,
but I haven't heard a word about Hinatsuru.
It was two days ago that the owner
of this House passed away, huh?
Everyone's gloomy,
and they're keeping their mouths shut.
Get that for me, will you?
I can't find my sash!
I'm so hungry!
Has the hairdresser arrived yet?
We have a crisis!
A young girl is crying!
Someone else is on their way.
Ogimoto House certainly has
no shortage of busybodies.
I have to find a way to let him know!
Lord Tengen!
Make a commotion, and I'll pulverize
all of the organs in your body.
That must be the food that woman left.
So it means that's Makio's room, huh?
It's odd. It feels so odd!
Is she in some kind of trouble now?
I can't tell.
I'm getting this slimy, creepy vibe, but...
Huh! Sitting here thinking
and not doing a thing...
That's not my style!
The wind...
Even though the windows are closed!
The attic...
Hey!
Damn you!
I'm onto you!
What the...
It's clattering around in the ceiling!
It's a demon just like I thought!
Where's it heading?
Where's it running off to?
OGIMOTO HOUSE
Out of my way!
I'm not letting you get away!
What's going on?
It's daytime, so it escaped up there.
But it has to climb down the walls
at some point!
Right there!
Hey! Now there's a sweet young thing—
You punched him!
Dammit! I messed up!
It's fleeing downstairs!
This way?
No.
It's this way!
Dammit!
It's hard to get a feel for it!
I lost sight of it!
Dammit!
It's all because people got in my way!
Hey! It's like a disaster struck here!
What happened in this room?
Huh?
W-Were you in a fight?
Are you okay?
Hey!
A-Are you all right?
Come on, settle down, okay?
I wasn't angry with you, all right?
Sorry about that.
If you're in any kind of trouble—
Hey you...
What are you doing in my room?
That's a demon standing behind me.
That's not what a human sounds like.
I didn't even notice her
until right before she spoke to me.
I-Is that even possible?
This sound is bad news,
but it's so quiet that I'm actually terrified!
This must be...
an U-Upper Rank demon, right?
Hey!
Are you hard of hearing or something?
W-Warabihime Oiran...
That girl just started here
the day before yesterday, so...
Hah! So what if she did?
Forgive me for entering
without permission!
The room's in such disarray,
and this girl was crying, so...
Could you be any uglier?
You really make me ill.
Wouldn't you be better off dead?
What's up with that hair color of yours?
Do you actually want to stand out?
This room is still in a shambles.
I thought I told you to clean it up.
Shut up!
Stop that screaming!
You clean up this room!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'll do it right now! Please forgive me!
What?
Please...
take your hands off her!
DEMON SLAYER: KIMETSU NO YAIBA
ENTERTAINMENT DISTRICT ARC
ENTERTAINMENT DISTRICT - TOKITO HOUSE
Madam, I've finished scrubbing the hallways,
and the mizukiri and mizuage for the flowers,
and changed the water!
What? Already?
What shall I do next?
N-Next? Um...
Here's a fresh cup of tea, Madam!
Oh, sorry to trouble you.
Not at all!
Madam, what next?
Madam!
Would you be quiet? Just hold on for a second!
You're a quick worker
and such a diligent child, aren't you?
That new girl went
and smashed up the house!
It looks like I need to teach that one
a harsh lesson!
Hey, Inoko!
What on earth are you doing?
I can't sense it even if I focus.
Where the hell did it go?
What did you say?
Let's hear you say that again.
Please take your hands off her.
Up close, you're even uglier than I thought.
Take your—
How dare you...
touch me!
TWO DAYS BEFORE
TANJIRO AND THE OTHERS
INFILTRATED
KYOGOKU HOUSE
I want you to stop it right now!
Stop what?
Stop causing people here to get hurt
and commit Ashinuke and suicide! That's what!
As for the ones who killed themselves,
you may as well have bullied them
to death, Warabihime!
That's a harsh thing to say, Madam.
You're not going to take my side, then?
You don't think it's their own fault
for irritating me?
Until now, I've looked the other way
more times than I can count!
But something's not right about you!
I can't protect you anymore!
And exactly whose earnings was it
that allowed this House to prosper so, you hag?
Years and years ago,
when I was still a child...
the old lady from the teahouse
told me a story.
She'd become profoundly forgetful,
but she told me about a certain Oiran.
She was incredibly beautiful,
but also incredibly twisted by nature.
The old lady said that she'd seen
such Oirans when she was a child,
and again,
when she was middle-aged.
YATAMAHIME
These Oirans were fond
of assuming names ending with "hime,"
and if anything were to irritate them,
they'd cock their heads to the side
and glare at you from below.
That was a unique habit they shared.
You!
Who are you?
Could it be...
th-that you...
You're not human?
That's the kind of thing...
that you should keep your mouth
shut about when you realize it.
It's the smart way to live.
That's how everyone's survived until now.
But it looks like you're far more stupid
than I ever thought.
It's a real pity, Omitsu.
UPPER SIX
There's no need for you
to be so scared!
The dried-out flesh of old hags
like you tastes horrible.
If it's ugly or dirty, there's no way
I'd ever put it in my mouth!
Goodbye, Omitsu.
Stop...
Stop!
What the...
She's dead!
She fell! Who is it?
No!
Isn't that the madam?
Hurry! Somebody call
the House Master right away!
How are you doing?
Master Muzan!
I can see that you've devoured
scores of humans.
You've gained
even more power than before.
That's a good thing.
Yes!
But you mustn't let your guard down.
The more things go your way, the more apt you are
to get the rug pulled out from under you.
Understood!
A skilled member of the Demon Slayer Corps,
a Hashira, could recognize us
as demons right away.
On the other hand, aside from those
as capable as Hashira,
we cannot see any differences
between humans at a glance.
Although we can distinguish them
by blood type, disease and genes...
Things that humans
have no knowledge of.
Daki...
Yes?
Yes, Master Muzan?
I have high hopes for you.
No one is as beautiful as you.
Nor as strong.
You've disposed of seven Hashira.
You're going to become
even more powerful from here on out.
You'll become cruel.
You're an extraordinary demon.
Don't you dare touch me
in such a familiar way!
Don't flatter yourself,
you rotten little punk!
It looks like you're in need of some discipline!
Some severe discipline!
Warabihime Oiran...
I beg of you.
Please.
Please forgive her.
It's almost time for us to open.
Our customers will be arriving.
I'll be sure to reprimand her harshly.
So please, for now...
Please, just help me save some face.
I suppose I may have lashed out
at this newcomer too mercilessly.
Tend to her wounds, please.
Master, please raise your head.
I'm the one who should be apologizing.
Lately, so many things
have left me feeling irritated.
I'm heading off to work,
so get this place tidied up right now.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Call for some help!
Get this room cleaned up!
Don't do anything that would
get on Warabihime Oiran's nerves!
That little brat...
From what I can sense,
his injuries are only minor.
Even though he's blacked out...
he went on the defensive.
He's no civilian.
He's probably with the Demon Slayer Corps!
That said, he doesn't have
the skill of a Hashira.
It took you a bit of time,
but you did a good job bringing him in.
Just keep them coming.
I'll be happy to kill and devour them all.
There's a murky scent in the air.
At night, in this city...
there's a murky scent in the air.
Zenko!
Thank goodness!
Are you okay, Zenko?
What happened to me?
You got punched, Zenko,
and you blacked out!
Oh...
That's right! My name is Zenko!
I had a dream that I'd become a man.
We brought you some food,
so be sure to have it.
Use this to cool down your cheek.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Are you okay?
Yes. It's not as bad as it looks.
I don't think.
Zenko, thank you.
Huh?
This is what you got for defending me.
Any man would rescue
a damsel in distress. That's a given.
Not that I'm a man, all right?
What I mean is, any human would, see?
For instance,
the eldest daughter or whatever!
I'm the eldest daughter, so I can't stand by
while a younger girl weeps! Not normally!
That's not true.
Everyone here has their hands full
just taking care of themselves.
We've never met
a kindhearted person like you before.
See you later, Zenko!
Take care of yourself!
Get lots of rest, okay?
Right.
Thanks!
NIN-NIN
Combined Junior
and Senior High School!
Tales of a Demon Slayer
Academy! Christmas Arc!
Today's the day I've been waiting for!
It's Christmas!
I've invited Nezuko to the Christmas party.
My planning was flawless. We can proceed
straight from the party to the wedding.
Hey, she's here! Nezuko's here!
EXCITED
Welcome! I've been waiting for you!
Thank you for inviting us to your party!
I did you a solid and showed up!
Merry Christmas.
FLAME
So what's Christmas? Tell me!
I never invited you guys!
And what's with those outfits?
Talk about mangling stuff up big time!
None of you have ever been invited
to a Christmas party, am I right?
Stop fooling around!
ZENITSU HAS NEVER BEEN INVITED, EITHER
Everyone except Nezuko, go home!
What did you say?
Tell me what Christmas is, dammit!
Shut up! Do you hear me?
TO BE CONTINUED