Hinatsuru!
EPISODE 5:
THINGS ARE GONNA GET REAL FLASHY!!
Forgive me, Lord Tengen.
Never mind. Stop talking.
I realized that Warabihime Oiran
was a demon,
but she became suspicious of me, as well.
So I drank some poison
and tried to slip out of the House.
But it seems this Belt that I was given by
Warabihime Oiran was for spying on and killing me.
So I was unable to contact you.
Lord Tengen, do not trouble yourself
with me. Please go now.
You heard that sound
just now, did you not?
The demon is on a rampage.
You're sure you're going to be all right?
Yes.
I am sorry I couldn't be of use to you.
There's no need for you
to do anything more.
Once the antidote starts working,
leave Yoshiwara.
You hear me?
Yes.
The battle has already begun.
Where is it?
Search for its presence!
It's here. Underground!
I can hear the sound of someone battling.
I can hear it well thanks
to the reverberations.
There's something here!
Sound Breathing...
First Form...
Roar!
UPPER SIX
What an infernal racket,
you piece of trash!
What is that sound?
What are you doing?
Where?
From the Ogimoto House?
And also Hinatsuru...
How many of you are here?
Four?
I'm not telling you!
If you tell me the truth,
I'd be willing to spare your life.
We clashed for maybe an instant,
but look at your sword!
It's already nicked.
Some hack of a swordsmith
must've forged that blade, am I right?
You're wrong!
The person who forged
this sword is amazing!
He's a brilliant swordsmith!
Then how did it get nicked, moron?
It's starting to get noisy
all over the place.
It's annoying me,
so this time, I'm going to kill you.
The blade gets nicked
when its wielder is subpar.
It's my fault!
I...
When all is said and done, I...
can't handle...
the Water Breathing technique!
My body's not suited for Water Breathing!
I can't become like Urokodaki or Tomioka
with the Water Breathing technique!
In my case...
I just can't help striking harder
with the Hinokami Kagura.
It's just compatible with my body!
But...
Would it kill you
to hold back a little, idiot?
That would be no way to train!
Hinokami Kagura!
Huh?
Flame Dance!
Clear Blue...
Tanjiro!
Tanjiro! Are you okay?
What? Are you hungry?
- Dummy!
- Huh?
- Boar!
Because of its sheer force...
I couldn't unleash multiple strikes.
Hang in there! I'll go fetch Shinobu!
It's different now!
I should be able to do it!
No!
I'm doing it!
That's what I've been training for!
Don't go down in defeat! Ablaze!
Ablaze! Ablaze!
Set your heart ablaze!
Hinokami Kagura...
Raging Sun!
His swordsmanship style just changed!
It's sharper than before.
What the hell is this sound?
Such an unpleasant sound!
The sound of breathing?
Flame Dance!
Flame Dance is a two-hit strike!
Even if she dodges it, there's one more!
That was nothing to write home about.
In the end, this is all it amounts to!
Where is he?
Hinokami Kagura...
Fake Rainbow...
An opening! The Opening Thread!
I can do this!
Hinokami Kagura...
Fire Wheel!
So slow. You're making me yawn.
Go on the defensive!
Defensive!
This is the fallout
from using the Hinokami Kagura!
All that built-up fatigue
is making my muscles tighten up!
Oh, so you're still alive?
Calm down.
Get your breathing under control!
Recover!
Hurry!
Recovery Breathing!
This Belt is like a powerful blade!
Even if I glimpse an Opening Thread,
it vanishes just like that!
My attacks are too slow!
Raise your body temperature!
Get your body temperature up!
I'm going to inform
Lady Shinobu, all right?
That your temperature
still hasn't gone down!
Kiyo, please! I'm begging you!
Keep it between us! I'm fine, okay?
But...
I'm feeling fine, see?
I'm fine! Never felt better!
Just look at this thermometer!
100.4 degrees!
Just like yesterday
and the day before that, remember?
It's been like that for days!
Uh...
If you have a fever that won't go down,
that means something's wrong!
I have no idea what I should do about it!
Only Lady Shinobu would know!
The thing is...
when I have a fever,
I'm at the top of my game!
I can unleash
multiple Hinokami Kagura strikes!
I might become even stronger!
Can't you wait just a little longer
before telling Lady Shinobu?
Just a little longer!
Just a little bit!
Very well.
But just a little longer, okay?
I can feel my temperature...
my body heat rising!
I'm able to fight...
an Upper Rank Demon!
You're a pesky one.
More than I thought you'd be.
This is entertaining.
I can do it!
Hinokami Kagura's effective!
No! It's not enough for it be effective!
I have to win!
Using every ounce of my power!
I'm gonna win, no matter what!
To protect them.
To protect lives!
Never again.
I won't let them be robbed for no reason.
Never again!
I won't let anyone...
suffer the same grief that we did!
You ugly people are still ugly,
even when you try so hard!
DEMON SLAYER: KIMETSU NO YAIBA
ENTERTAINMENT DISTRICT ARC
OGIMOTO HOUSE
SOMEWHAT EARLIER
What's going on?
It's a monster! A monster!
Hey, go get ready for work!
There's a monster boar that's
demolishing the ceilings and the floors!
Huh?
How is that even possible?
Then come with me!
I'm totally feeling the demon's presence!
Is it here?
Found it!
The hole leading to the demon's lair!
Get ready to die!
Ugh!
So I can only get my head inside, huh?
Nice try! That won't work
on Lord Inosuke!
I'm a man who can dislocate all his joints!
In other words, as long as my head fits,
there's nowhere that I can't go!
Comin' through! No one can stop me!
Freakin' long! This is no game trail!
A demon!
There's a demon here!
What the heck is this?
Huh? A cloth with a human pattern?
What is this?
No, this feels like...
those are living humans.
So it traps humans
inside a woman's belly band, huh?
Damn. Then it takes them out
whenever it wants, and devours them?
Pretty savage, if you ask me.
What's he doing here?
No, what are you doing?
Barging in on someone else's food locker...
So dirty!
How dirty you are!
Dirty!
Smelly! You damn stinkbug!
What did you say, you worm? So gross!
Why, you damn stinkbug!
Wriggle, wriggle, wriggle, wriggle!
You're really grossing me out, Worm Belt!
Look how sluggish you are!
You got greedy
and swallowed up too many humans!
An attack by an overweight worm...
will never land on Lord Inosuke!
Grow a spine...
and don't come back until you're ready!
Damn! He managed to slice me
without touching the humans!
After I went to the trouble
of storing all that fresh food!
His intuition is razor-sharp!
Especially his ability to detect
murderous intent is extraordinary!
So sensitive...
he can perceive attacks
from any direction and dodge them!
I never expected a Demon Slayer
to infiltrate the food locker.
What should I do?
Capture him alive.
UPPER SIX
He's the one who got in my way
when I captured Makio.
He was beautiful.
Except for the ten most beautiful,
you can kill the humans you've stored.
Though it might prove harder to capture
them alive than to merely kill them...
Devour some of the ones there
and strengthen your body.
I can't slash it!
Because it's bending like that?
Beast Breathing, Sixth Fang...
Palisade Bite!
It won't do any good to slash me.
I'm not the main body.
Never mind that. You're leaving the humans
you saved in the lurch. Is that what you want?
Whatever you do to me,
I can get it back in a flash!
Oh, crap! I have to fight it
while protecting those humans!
Dammit!
I can't keep up!
You damn Worm Belt!
You came up with a great name!
"Worm Belt"!
It really is gross!
You're absolutely right!
I'm so going to tell Lord Tengen on you!
We're going to give you a hand...
so fight the good fight, Boar Head!
Who the heck are you?
We're Uzui's wives!
I'm not much of a fighter!
So please don't get your hopes up!
Suma! Don't be such a wimp!
But... But... Makio, you know
I'm a good-for-nothing!
I mean, I got captured right away!
It's too much to ask of me!
Protecting everyone who got caught!
I'm the most liable to die first!
That's right! How astute you are!
Now then, which one
of you should I eat first?
Damn that thing!
It's not the main body?
If that's true, I'm screwed!
This battle's never gonna end!
Thunder Breathing...
First Form...
Thunderclap and Flash.
Sixfold.
Maybe you should stay asleep
the whole time.
THE ONES WHO DELIVERED
ZENITSU'S SWORD
- Muscle!
Is that kid a Demon Slayer, too?
Why is he dressed like an idiot?
I have no idea!
Hey! The next one's coming! Move!
Who is that boy?
Such blistering speed!
No, forget that.
Didn't I just hear two sounds?
A noise like overlapping thunderbolts,
creating two sounds.
One was that boy.
The other one...
came from above?
The wind?
Did an air hole open up?
What can you do from aboveground
to create a hole all the way down here?
What the hell?
He's here.
Someone just came inside.
DESTROYER
OF DEMONS
This presence!
A Hashira!
Lord Tengen...
DESTROY
Makio...
Suma...
Sorry I took so long.
It's a relief to see you looking good!
He wasn't like this before.
The thought of dying didn't bother me.
Since that was how I was trained.
Because I was a shinobi.
Especially since a kunoichi could never hope
to match a male shinobi in terms of strength.
Staking my life was something
I only needed minimal effort to do.
I want you three
to only think about your own lives.
Above all else, your top priority
is to come back to me.
Life over accomplishing your mission!
What I'm saying is at odds with this occupation,
but it doesn't matter. I'm allowing it!
The order that lives should go in
is flashy and clear-cut in my mind.
First, you three.
Second, law-abiding citizens.
And finally, me.
As a Demon Slayer, it goes without saying that I'll also
protect the public leading their nonchalant, drab lives...
but to be blunt in my flashy way,
you three are more important to me.
So don't die on me.
Is it really okay to go around saying that?
If you put your own life first, you can't
get much serious work done. Is that okay?
I think it's okay.
If Lord Tengen says he's fine with it.
Not wanting to die
or wanting to go on living...
I'm sure it's not wrong
to feel that way, either.
As long as you don't despise yourself,
it should be fine.
I'm sure.
You're right.
I see that you've been doing
some flashy work.
You're my wives, all right!
All right!
Starting now,
things are going to get real flashy!
NIN-NIN
Nin-nin!
The Sound Hashira
can't possibly have three wives!
Well, why don't you try
for that, too, Zenitsu?
What? Really?
Okay, then, there's Yoshiko, Sanae,
and then there's...
I have to let Nezuko know.
Tanjiro!
Now, it's time for a Taisho-era secret!
Uzui's family practices polygamy,
and I hear that when you turn 15,
the head of the family picks out three
wives who are sure to be compatible.
But they say Suma stepped forward herself.
Maybe I should become a shinobi, too!
Then you'll be starting
shinobi training today, right?
Huh?
Nooooo!
Next, Episode 6, "Layered Memories."
TO BE CONTINUED