KILL
What the hell is this?
After the castles got worn down
from the Restoration,
this one, being in such a remote area,
must've been abandoned and forgotten.
That's my guess.
This pisses me off.
Knowing that those demon bastards
are living it up like lords.
Are you sure that someone
from the village was taken here?
Yes!
Last night, we tracked her to the inside
of the castle tower but found nothing.
She wouldn't vanish
into thin air, you moron!
How could you let them
ditch you so fast?
I'm truly sorry!
So, another woman disappeared today.
Despite the Demon Slayer Corps
being on the alert... right under our noses...
No one's expecting anything
from you scrubs.
As it turns out...
we may not have gotten here
too late after all.
Bastard!
It looks like I should've disposed
of them last night!
DESTROY
Take this!
You two, head back.
I'll be going on ahead
with the Wind Hashira.
But...
You're a hindrance, all right?
Now get out of here!
Shinazugawa...
Something's not right.
Yeah. I don't like this, either.
I've never seen demons
swarming around like this.
Help me!
Wind Breathing...
Second Form...
Claws-Purifying Wind!
Serpent Breathing...
Fifth Form...
Slithering Serpent!
That was close.
Who asked for your help?
So powerful!
They're not just any Demon Slayers!
Are they Hashira?
Help me!
Hey, demon!
You can just leave that woman
along with your head!
Outta my way!
They just keep coming!
What are you, cockroaches? Take this!
Again?
Where the hell are these things coming from?
Save the woman, Shinazugawa.
I'll take over here.
Yeah, I'm getting sick of slashing them.
I'll let you have this one!
Serpent Breathing, Third Form...
Coil Choke.
Hey!
You still can't win
even with all your foot soldiers.
Just surrender and...
die.
Wind Breathing...
Fourth Form...
Rising Dust Storm!
Really now...
If you want her that much...
Stop it! What are you doing?
...take her!
What's this?
Come back here, you bastard!
What the hell's going on?
Hey, Shinazugawa, what was that?
Where did the demons go?
How should I know?
Are you sure I can drop you off
at the crossroads up ahead?
KOCHO
Ms. Kanao!
Welcome back from your mission!
- Welcome back!
Master...
I have just returned.
The incident
at the Swordsmith Village...
is as I described
the other day.
Thanks to the efforts of Mr. Tokito, Ms. Kanroji,
as well as that of Kamado and the others,
we were able to defeat two Upper Ranks.
Not only that...
but Ms. Nezuko conquered the sun.
This signals that some major
developments are on the horizon.
Yes.
Most likely, Muzan Kibutsuji
will send his demons...
to abduct Ms. Nezuko.
So that he can take possession
of the demon who's conquered the sun.
As an emergency Hashira Meeting
has been called...
I will be heading
to the Ubuyashiki Mansion.
May I entrust Ms. Nezuko to your care
while I'm gone, Kanao?
I'm counting on you!
DEMON SLAYER: KIMETSU NO YAIBA
HASHIRA TRAINING ARC
Really?
So, they're moving it already.
Is everyone in the village okay?
I don't know the details, but since they're worried
that more demons might come during the night,
they've been working nonstop
to get the place restored and moved.
I see.
It's a miracle that it wasn't worse
after two Upper Ranks showed up.
They sure were unbelievable opponents.
The Demon Slayer Corps have a few so-called
empty villages built for such occasions.
So that they can move right away
if anything happens.
Really?
Well, it just goes to show that the Master
and the others were that farsighted.
But listen.
Are you sure you should be gorging yourself
like that after being unconscious for seven days?
KAKUSHI
Yes! Because Ms. Kanroji said
she always eats plenty!
Well, if you ask me, that one
is actually something of an outlier.
Delicious!
Is it true that Ms. Love and Mr. Mist were asleep for
two days, then mostly recovered by Day Three?
Yes! I respect them!
So, you're inching
closer to their level.
Little by little.
Well, if you're gonna get well
faster, it's all good.
Yes.
Thank goodness everyone survived, huh?
Yes!
Hey, this is what I've been dying to ask you!
I hear that something mind-blowing happened
to your little sister. Is she okay?
Uh, yes.
She's been strolling around
under the sun, hasn't she?
That's a big deal, right?
Isn't that, like, a really big deal?
We're having someone look into it,
but it's not clear.
Whether she's starting to turn back
into a human or evolving as a demon.
Is it Lady Kocho who's looking into that?
No, it's Ms. Tamayo!
Who's Ms. Tamayo?
Hey, come on! I told you,
you shouldn't stuff your face like that!
You're still recovering, so show some restraint!
What a close call!
Since that's happened to your little sister,
a lot will be happening for sure.
The Demon Slayer swordsmen
have been ordered to go on alert,
and I'm told that the Hashira
are meeting right now.
Seriously, what's going to happen?
Are we the last to show up?
I see that we've kept you waiting.
Forgive us.
STONE HASHIRA
GYOMEI HIMEJIMA
It's fine.
Good work
on fulfilling your mission.
Sure thing.
WIND HASHIRA
SANEMI SHINAZUGAWA
Kanroji and Tokito...
I hear that you battled
some Upper Ranks.
Yes, it was really intense!
LOVE HASHIRA
MITSURI KANROJI
I was, like, "I'm done for!"...
but we all put
our strength together!
Right, Muichiro?
MIST HASHIRA
MUICHIRO TOKITO
Yes.
Man, I wish I'd been there.
How come I never run into any Upper Ranks?
You'll just have to resign
yourself to fate.
SERPENT HASHIRA
OBANAI IGURO
If you don't encounter them,
you never will.
Kanroji and Tokito...
How've you been since then physically?
Oh, right!
Thanks! I'm feeling much better now!
Wow! He's worried about me!
So am I. Although I'm not yet 100 percent.
Losing any more Hashira would put
the Demon Slayer Corps at risk.
Defeating two Upper Ranks without losing
your own lives was noble of you.
About the two of you...
INSECT HASHIRA
SHINOBU KOCHO
Your wounds healed
at an abnormally fast pace this time.
What happened to you?
The Master himself will surely
address that matter, as well.
WATER HASHIRA
GIYU TOMIOKA
Thank you for waiting for so long.
Today's Hashira Meeting will be presided over
by myself, Amane Ubuyashiki...
in Kagaya Ubuyashiki's stead.
And also, due to the fact
that his condition has worsened,
the head of our family, Kagaya,
can never appear before you again.
Please allow me to express
my heartfelt apologies.
Understood.
I shall pray that the Master
will find the strength...
to let the light of his life burn on
even one day longer.
Lady Amane, please stay strong yourself.
I would like to thank you Hashira
from the bottom of my heart.
I believe you're already aware of this...
but now that a demon
who's conquered sunlight has appeared...
it's a given that Muzan Kibutsuji will make
a frenzied attempt to come after her.
So that he, too, can conquer the sun.
An all-out war of immense scale
is approaching.
While battling Upper Four and Upper Five...
Lady Kanroji...
Lord Tokito...
I was told that a unique-looking mark
appeared on you both.
Please instruct us as to what conditions
you met to induce those marks.
Marks?
During the Sengoku Period...
the swordsmen who'd driven Muzan Kibutsuji
to the brink of defeat...
the swordsmen of First Breathing...
It is said that every one of them came to bear
a mark similar to demonic patterns.
There are those who are aware of this,
having heard through word of mouth.
This is the first I'm hearing of it.
Why was it kept secret?
There were many who brooded
over not having the mark appear.
That is why.
Much of the lore surrounding
this mark remains vague.
Perhaps because at the time,
it was not seen as vital enough to preserve.
Or perhaps because there was
no one to pass it on...
during the many times
the Demon Slayer Corps faced annihilation.
There is only a single explicit record
remaining today.
"When one person
bearing the mark appears,
those around him also manifest marks
as if resonating with him."
So wrote one of the First Breathing swordsmen
in his personal notes.
The first person of our generation
to have the mark appear...
though not a Hashira...
is Lord Tanjiro Kamado.
He is the first to bear the mark.
It felt like my body
was going "Pow!" and "Bam!"
However, as he himself seemed unable
to describe exactly how his mark appeared...
And my stomach went "Clench, clench!"
My stomach went "Clench"!
we decided to revisit it another time.
And now, following Lord Kamado,
two Hashira have manifested the mark.
Please enlighten us,
Lady Kanroji, Lord Tokito.
Huh?
Oh, right!
Lady Amane is so gorgeous!
Um, um, um, you see, when it happened...
I know that...
my body felt extremely light!
Let's see.
Um...
And then...
I felt my body go, "Bam!"
It went "Bam!"...
and then "Pow!"
My heart was pounding like crazy!
And my ears were going "Ding"!
Then, "Ripple, ripple, ripple!"
Huh?
I'm so sorry!
I wish I could crawl into a hole!
TANJIRO TYPE
Then, let me speak.
It's not as if I was aware of the mark...
but when I looked back on that battle...
several things did come to mind.
Things that were out of the ordinary.
As long as certain
conditions are met...
I believe that the mark
will appear on everyone.
I will now explain how to do so.
During the previous battle,
I was poisoned and unable to move.
I tried to slow the flow of the poison
by using my breathing technique...
but then, the boy who tried to save me
was about to be killed...
which brought back
my memories of the past.
And the overwhelming rage I felt
made me lose control of my emotions.
I believe that my heart rate exceeded
200 beats per minute at that moment.
Not only that, but my body felt
as though it was on fire...
and I'm sure that my temperature
was over 102 degrees.
How could you move in such a state?
That would be fatal!
Yes, that's true.
So, I think that's the point
at which we get culled.
Whether you die or survive
in that moment...
is likely the difference between those
who manifest the mark and those who don't.
A heart rate exceeding
200 beats per minute...
And how do you know
your temperature was over 102 degrees?
Right. When I was being treated
at Ms. Kocho's, I had a fever...
and the reading taken by a thermometer...
102 degrees...
was the same as my body heat
when my mark supposedly appeared.
Is that right?
Hah! Could it be any simpler?
Having such a simple mind
that you can call this simple...
I envy you.
What was that?
Nothing.
So...
the Hashira's top priority
is to awaken these marks, right?
Very well.
We will figure out a way...
so please let the Master know
that he may rest assured.
Thank you very much.
However, I do need to convey one thing to you
regarding this mark training.
What would that be?
Those whose marks have already appeared
have no choice in the matter, but...
all who have a mark will,
without exception...
I see.
But in that case,
what will become of me?
Good Lord...
Now that Lady Amane has left the room,
I'll be taking off.
Hey, hold up!
You're not going anywhere.
We need to decide
what our respective roles will be!
The six of you should discuss that.
It has nothing to do with me.
What do you mean, nothing to do with you?
You seem to forget that you're a Hashira.
Or what is this?
Do you intend to get yourself
a head start on training?
Skipping this meeting no less?
O-O-Oh!
Look, you! Get back here!
Mr. Tomioka, please explain yourself.
We can't just dismiss this without reason.
I'm not like the rest of you.
I don't like the sound of that.
You said the same thing before,
didn't you, Tomioka?
You're looking down on us?
N-No fighting, all right?
Calm down!
Get the hell back here!
Oh! No, no, no!
Stop!
Sit down.
We're continuing this discussion.
I have a proposal.
Here.
Wow!
Thank you so much!
Jeez, you sure have an appetite!
Hey, where are those
three little ones and your little sister?
I haven't seen Aoi, either.
Since there aren't any Demon Slayer swordsmen
in critical condition now,
they've been playing
with Nezuko all this time.
Because of that, she's starting
to speak little by little!
Hey, is that right?
Sounds peaceful.
This rice dumpling tastes great, too!
Yeah, yeah, I hear you, okay? But...
if that yellow-haired kid comes around,
there's going to be trouble, right?
Ouch!
Oh my, Mr. Zenitsu!
Are you back from your mission?
Kiyo! I'm back!
Everyone! Mr. Zenitsu's back!
Oh!
Mr. Zenitsu!
Thank you for your hard work!
- Thank you for your hard work!
Kiyo! Naho! Sumi!
You've gathered here just for me, huh?
Man, this one was another doozy...
and I thought, "I'm gonna die!
I'm gonna die!" over and over!
But then I thought how devastated
you'd all be if I did die...
so I pushed through it!
I mean, you'd be sad without me, right?
Not really, no!
Huh?
But we're glad you've returned alive!
Uh, yeah.
Oh, Mr. Zenitsu... So, you're back?
Thank you for your hard work.
Ms. Aoi!
You missed me
while I was gone, didn't you?
Right? You missed me, didn't you?
I don't know if I'd put it like that.
W-Welcome home!
So loud!
W-Welcome back!
You're so adorable I'm gonna die!
Oh, please, go right ahead!
What's going on with you, Nezuko?
You're actually talking!
For me? You worked at it for me, right?
That makes me so happy!
Please go somewhere else!
Does this mean you and I
are getting married at last?
Get away from her!
You were a lovely sight to see
in the moonlight,
but in the sunlight,
you're crazy gorgeous! Magnificent!
When we're married, I'll see to it
that you have sushi and eel every day,
so you can marry me with no worries!
Welcome home, Inosuke!
"I... nosuke"?
Inosuke, welcome home!
Where is that guy?
I think I'll go kill him!
Don't talk like that!
Come to think of it,
where's that boar head boy?
Inosuke?
Huh? He was around this morning.
Your little sister has been getting schooled
by the boar head.
What would that be?
What would it be?
Inosuke, Inosuke, Inosuke, Inosuke!
Imosuke, Imofuke!
Big Boss Inosuke!
Big Boss Imosuke!
Inosuke, Inosuke, Inosuke, Inosuke!
And he was intent
on making her learn his name.
Really? I had no idea that was going on!
By the way, do you have
any more of these rice dumplings?
You're not done eating yet?
Hey!
Mr. Haganezuka!
Have your wounds healed?
Thank goodness!
Are you not feeling all right?
Oh, my sword.
Thank you very much.
That's Mr. Rengoku's sword guard!
Thank you very much...
for protecting Kotetsu.
Why don't you sit down now?
Are you all right?
Bla... Bla... Bla...
Blade? Yes, I'll look
at the sword blade, too!
Oh!
Wow!
It's an even deeper shade
of pitch black!
That's some high-quality steel there...
so the swordsman who wielded it
must've been exceptionally strong.
DESTROY
The character for "destroy"...
The swordsmith who forged this
meant for it to destroy all demons!
He didn't even engrave his name
as its creator! Just this one character!
DESTROYER OF DEMONS
The hierarchy system started
after this sword was forged, I'm told,
and only the Hashira came to have the words
"Destroyer of Demons" engraved on their swords.
I didn't know that!
So, it's an amazing sword!
But when I fought in the previous battle,
I don't remember seeing this character.
Hah!
I told you... that's because I hadn't even
finished the first stage of honing...
when you guys took it away and used it!
I hadn't removed all the rust yet, okay?
I'm gonna kill you!
I'm so sorry!
My wounds still haven't fully healed,
and I can't stop my tears from flowing!
Man, it hurts so bad,
I can't take it anymore!
Thanks to all the interruptions, I had to start
honing again from scratch, all right?
Yeah, but in terms of severity,
the kid's injuries are just as bad as yours.
I mean, the bones in his body
got totally pulverized.
I'm gonna kill you!
Can't you have a conversation?
Listen to me, Tanjiro!
You're gonna bring me rice dumplings
until the day you die!
You hear me? Do you understand?
Y-Yes! I'll bring them to you!
Thank you so much!
Please take care!
I've heard the rumors about him,
but he sure is a piece of work.
He was awfully mild today.
It looks like he's in a lot of pain.
Seriously?
Can you be any noisier?
Hey...
Sorry, Genya.
We're done now.
Sorry to make such a—
Whoa! Inosuke!
What are you doing,
breaking the window?
Are you a moron or what?
Lady Kocho's going to kill you!
Shut up!
Comin' through!
I wish they'd put me in another room.
Training, training, training!
The group strength training program
is about to start!
The group strength training?
The strongest will gather and give training...
and something or other, they said!
Huh? What's that about?
I have no idea!
I see.
As far as the Hashira Training
for the Demon Slayer swordsmen is concerned...
I think we've worked out
most of the details of our strategy.
What about the duration and start date?
Let us start in three days' time.
That's so soon. Can we do that?
We have no time to lose.
As we have no way of knowing
what moves Muzan Kibutsuji will be making...
I'd like us to be prepared
in every possible way.
If the demons start running rampant again...
it will be too much
for us Hashira to handle.
But what if the demons strike
while we're training?
We can assume that the demons' focus
will be on capturing Nezuko Kamado.
As a matter of fact, ever since the incident
at the Swordsmith Village,
demon sightings have dwindled considerably.
If that's the case...
as Hashira, we never had any time until now
to train anyone but our own Tsuguko...
but over a short span, it will be a chance to go all out
to raise the bar of the entire Demon Slayer Corps.
This is a crucial, pressing need.
Crucial.
Due to this line of thinking,
I have proposed this Hashira Training.
Mr. Himejima...
You don't have to go on and on about it.
I am also in agreement.
I have no objections, either.
Neither do I.
I'm fine with it, too!
Can the training be handled
by just us active Hashira?
I'm thinking of asking the retired Hashira
to help out, as well.
No objections to that, either?
None, of course.
All that's left...
is Mr. Tomioka, right?
I finally get back from my mission,
and now we have to train.
This is so miserable.
Are you heading there now, Zenitsu?
That's right. We're going to train
under every Hashira one by one!
What, really? That's great!
There's nothing great about it.
It's awful! It's hell!
Whoever came up with this idea?
Just die, will you?
Hey!
Getting to train with someone ranked above you
is a shortcut to improving your skills!
When you take on someone
stronger than you...
you absorb it all,
and that makes you stronger!
If you're going to spew such positive drivel,
as of today, you and I are no longer friends!
Ow, ow, ow!
It's all well and good for you!
Since your broken bones haven't healed yet,
you get to lie in that comfy bed all day!
But I have to head out there now!
Do you understand how that feels?
Sorry!
Hah!
Hey, Zenitsu!
Don't even think about talking to me!
No, wait a second!
I forgot to tell you something.
Thanks!
During the battle against Upper Four...
when I could no longer use one of my legs...
I used the Thunder Breathing technique
you once taught me...
and that's how I was able
to behead the demon!
Of course, I couldn't do it
as fast as you...
but really, thanks!
See, there are times when your connections
to others can get you out of a jam...
so everything you learn
during Hashira Training...
will probably lead you
to a brighter future.
Oh, you dummy!
Just don't think that saying stuff like that
will put me in a better mood!
Hey, he's in a good mood!
Thank goodness!
See you, Tanjiro! Feel better soon!
Seriously! Everyone's so helpless
without me around!
Really, thank you so much...
Zenitsu.
Too slow! Too slow! Too slow! Too slow!
What the hell are you doing, you punks?
This makes no sense whatsoever!
For starters, you're sorely lacking
in basic physical stamina!
Running is such a simple task!
Faster! Move like you're being chased by a demon!
All right, now! What, you're speechless?
Who told you to crawl on your belly?
It's not break time yet!
Go do another lap!
I'm done.
What am I gonna do with you?
The training by the currently active Hashira
will be even harsher than this!
Lord Tengen does seem
so much more alive on the front lines.
Sure, why wouldn't he be?
We've got to help him as much as we can!
They'll be famished,
so let's make tons and tons of rice balls!
- Right!
Lord Tengen!
Lunch is ready!
Okay!
Hey, you guys, it's lunchtime!
I can't...
I can't even think of eating!
How pathetic are you?
Lord Tengen, don't be so angry with them.
I wish I didn't have to...
but if I send them like this to the next Hashira,
they're gonna lay all the blame on me.
Here you go, Lord Tengen.
Right!
Miso soup loaded with salt!
This is nothing compared
to their training sessions! Seriously!
You're in charge of boosting
their basic physical stamina, right?
What kind of training
do they have in store after this?
Well, after this...
first, they'll undergo
Tokito's Rapid Movement Training.
That guy can have a deadpan look
on his face while being super-harsh.
Next up is Kanroji's
Flexibility Training from hell.
Then, it's on to Iguro.
He'll rework their sword skills.
That serpent's one incessant trainer!
Then, we have Shinazugawa.
I hear it's called
"Infinite Slashing Training"...
but just as the name implies,
there'll be no end to it, I bet.
Last but not least, Mister Himejima's
Muscle Amplification Training.
No choice but to become superhuman
at that point.
For the Hashira, too, since they'll be taking on
an endless stream of Demon Slayer swordsmen,
they can count on boosting
their own physical stamina!
Well? Flashy, isn't it?
I sure would've liked to try my hand
at all-out training, too.
I'm counting on you, you guys.
Come on, guys!
At this rate,
my temperature's never gonna go up!
You're so damn weak!
That's right! Just keep that up!
Let's spread them a little more, okay?
There's no telling
where the enemy will attack from.
Feel it.
Your stance is so full of holes, a demon
would've devoured you three times by now.
In order to maintain my marked state...
Look, you're vulnerable from the side.
Everyone, strive to do your best.
This is all for the sake
of destroying demons.
We do this...
for the Master's sake.
For the sake of all the Demon Slayer swordsmen
who've lost their lives.
For the sake of all living people.
We must see this through to the end.
We must strive.
What's going on?
Ow! I'm bleeding!
What's this all of a sudden?
How could you?
Rush! Rush!
This is a letter from the Master.
Read it without delay.
A letter? To me? He took the time to...
Huh?
What is it?
Mr. Tomioka...
is not taking part
in the Hashira Training?
Master Kagaya...
It seems that the Hashira,
to prepare for the coming battle,
have started a Hashira Training program
for the Demon Slayer swordsmen.
Your children...
are carrying out your will...
and are making sure
that your hopes live on.
For the sake of your ardent desire
to defeat Muzan Kibutsuji...
they are willingly taking the next steps.
Amane...
Yes?
For all that you've done...
thank you...
from the bottom of my heart.
Yes!
STATE OF PROGRESS
Good evening, Ms. Tamayo.
It's dangerous, you know.
Leaving your window open at night.
But tonight, the moon
is truly gorgeous to behold.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm one of Kagaya Ubuyashiki's messengers.
But really, you're quite adept at hiding.
In the time that it took to find you,
Ubuyashiki has become immobile.
How did you find this place?
That would be due to human connections.
I was able to identify the former owner
of this house you've purchased.
Not only that, but I kept an eye
on Yushiro during the day.
I may have received training...
but I am a mere crow.
No one would ever be that wary of me.
As I have no intention of harming you,
please rest assured.
Then, what is it that you want with me?
Hmm.
You're full of suspicion.
I don't blame you.
It would be hard to gain
your trust like Tanjiro has.
Just as I thought.
What does he intend to do?
Ubuyashiki...
Is he trying to deceive me somehow?
Where is Yushiro?
You need not worry about Yushiro.
Listen.
You can hear his footsteps
running toward us.
And now...
shall I state my business?
There is a girl in the Demon Slayer Corps...
who is also well-versed
in demon physiology and pharmaceuticals.
Along with looking into the changes to Nezuko,
we want you to collaborate with her.
Will you work with us
to defeat Muzan Kibutsuji?
Please come to the Ubuyashiki Mansion.
You're summoning me, a demon...
to the Demon Slayer Corps headquarters?
EPISODE 1:
TO DEFEAT MUZAN KIBUTSUJI
PART 1
Every week during the Hashira Training Arc...
I'm going to let you in on a Taisho-era secret
about each Hashira!
Inosuke?
What are you going to do
about this broken glass?
Yeah, but...
Bad boy!
You're always positive,
and that's what I like about you...
but there are things that you mustn't do.
Now, then, hold up your arm.
Let me tend to your wound.
Don't ever do anything
like this again, all right?
Howa... Howa...
Ms. Shinobu is strict
when she needs to be...
but she's bursting with compassion.
Like at the Hashira Meeting the other day.
Ms. Kanroji?
Huh? Oh, thank you!
You're welcome.
That's it for today's Taisho-era secret!
Next, Episode 2...
"Water Hashira Giyu Tomioka's Pain."
TO BE CONTINUED